<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>quartz crystal &#8211; Nuage Showroom</title>
	<atom:link href="http://nuage21.com/product-tag/quartz-crystal/feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://nuage21.com</link>
	<description>Our Clothing &#38; Accessories</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 01:55:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Tsumi Hematite and Quartz Crystal Bracelet TS142</title>
		<link>http://nuage21.com/product/tsumi-hematite-and-mineral-quartz-necklace-ts142</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2016 15:30:18 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onewithclouds]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://nuage21.com/?post_type=product&#038;p=67</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>This absolutely fabulous bracelet is inspired by the notion of protection and armor. The unrivaled design of this bracelet owes much to designer's bold and authentic creative vision, as well as impeccable and flawless execution. This bracelet is aptly created in monochrome on the premise of minimal design and outstanding selection of materials. The latter seems to give prominence to this bracelet's original composition through hematite beads that encircle and accentuate the bracelet's most refined and interesting detail - a genuine crystal of Quartz.</p>
<p>Materials: Hematite, Quartz, Metal Elements, Sterling Silver Logo Charm. Length - 19.5 cm (7.67").</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://nuage21.com/product/tsumi-hematite-and-mineral-quartz-necklace-ts142">Tsumi Hematite and Quartz Crystal Bracelet TS142</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://nuage21.com">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This absolutely fabulous bracelet is inspired by the notion of protection and armor. The unrivaled design of this bracelet owes much to designer&#8217;s bold and authentic creative vision, as well as impeccable and flawless execution. This bracelet is aptly created in monochrome on the premise of minimal design and outstanding selection of materials. The latter seems to give prominence to this bracelet&#8217;s original composition through hematite beads that encircle and accentuate the bracelet&#8217;s most refined and interesting detail &#8211; a genuine crystal of Quartz.</p>
<h4>Materials</h4>
<p>Quartz Crystals or Rock Crystals are one of the most beautiful and yet most common types of crystal found on the planet. While often referred to as &#8216;clear quartz&#8217;, the crystals can actually range from clear to cloudy to almost completely opaque. The configurations and shapes they occur in are also numerous. Quartz is one of the most universal crystals that is often believed to be able to amplify feelings, emotions, thoughts and positive affirmations. It is also used to enhance the effects of other crystals and minerals it is used with.</p>
<p>Hematite is one of the prettiest and most unique crystals used in jewelry accessories. This crystal provides a unique combination of shiny charisma, while retaining the ability to remain reserved. It is one of the few magnetic crystals the structure of which is dominated by iron. Hematite is often referred to as a ‘seeker crystal’ that helps one find a new path or approach to gain something you desire, but not yet posses. Hematite crystals are thought to have great grounding and balancing effect, as well as serving to stimulate mind, memory, sometimes evoking deep thought.</p>
<p>Materials: Hematite, Quartz, Metal Elements, Sterling Silver Logo Charm. Medium length &#8211; 19.5 cm.</p>
<h4>About Tsumi</h4>
<p>Tsumi is a brand born from the love of fashion, as well as an inherent need to be original and unique. Each Tsumi accessory is infused by a touch of authentic ethnic flair and is inspired by joyful memories of traveling the world. Tsumi accessories are crafted with an incredible skill, while remaining visionary and creative pieces of contemporary jewelry.</p>
<p>Most of Tsumi accessories are made in either limited quantity or in one unique specimen. Tsumi is also synonymous with an exceptional selection of original and rare materials used to create their stylish accessories. These include semi-precious stones, corals, pearls and crystals, making Tsumi jewelry not only an embodiment of original style, but also an experience.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://nuage21.com/product/tsumi-hematite-and-mineral-quartz-necklace-ts142">Tsumi Hematite and Quartz Crystal Bracelet TS142</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://nuage21.com">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
