<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Rings &#8211; Nuage Showroom</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/wpstatic/product-category/rings/feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://localhost/wpstatic</link>
	<description>Our Clothing &#38; Accessories</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 01:55:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Francoise Oz Faience Ring with Black Glazing FR01</title>
		<link>http://localhost/wpstatic/product/francoise-oz-faience-ring-black-glossy-glazing-fr01</link>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2016 19:41:17 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onewithclouds]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/wpstatic/?post_type=product&#038;p=351</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>This beautiful one-of-a-kind ring is the definition of an original accessory. It has a sense of true presence, which it conveys through its beautifully organic design. One might infer that the design is fantasy-inspired, yet the ring is very real. This particular example of Francoise Oz creativity and craftsmanship is a larger type of ring. The latter might be the reason why it is giving off a spectacular wearable sculpture vibe.</p>
<p>Francoise Oz rings are exclusives that come in only one ring size, listed below. We highly recommend you to consider <a href="http://www.ringsizes.co/info.html" target="_blank">the factors outlined here</a> when determining your ring size, as well as consulting this <a href="http://www.ringsizes.co/" target="_blank">excellent ring size conversion chart</a>. If you need help determining your ring size, contact us through the chat app on this site.</p>
<p>[table id=9 /]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic/product/francoise-oz-faience-ring-black-glossy-glazing-fr01">Francoise Oz Faience Ring with Black Glazing FR01</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This beautiful one-of-a-kind ring is the definition of an original accessory. It has a sense of true presence, which it conveys through its beautiful organic design. One might infer that the design is fantasy-inspired, yet the ring feels very real. This particular example of Francoise Oz creativity and craftsmanship is a larger type of ring. The latter might be the reason why it is giving off a spectacular wearable sculpture vibe.</p>
<h4>About Francoise Oz</h4>
<p>Francoise Oz is an exquisite contemporary wearable sculpture brand with a distinct, unconventional, contemporary aesthetic. The process of creation of jewelry from faience and clay, employed by Francoise Oz is meticulous and labor-intensive. Francoise Oz&#8217;s wonderful creations are taking shape through forming raw material, firing, then grinding the fired earthenware pieces by hand and glazing. The resulting pieces are stylish, artistic and absolutely unique. No wonder, Francoise Oz&#8217;s faience and ceramic accessories are endorsed by fashion and design connoisseurs worldwide.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic/product/francoise-oz-faience-ring-black-glossy-glazing-fr01">Francoise Oz Faience Ring with Black Glazing FR01</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Francoise Oz Faience Ring with Black Glazing FR02</title>
		<link>http://localhost/wpstatic/product/francoise-oz-faience-ring-with-black-glazing-fr02</link>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2016 20:55:06 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onewithclouds]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/wpstatic/?post_type=product&#038;p=381</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>This beautiful one-of-a-kind ring is the definition of an original accessory. It has a sense of true presence, which it conveys through its beautifully organic design. One might infer that the design is fantasy-inspired, yet the ring is very real. This particular example of creativity and craftsmanship is different from its Francoise Oz counterparts, as it is smaller than the rest of its siblings. Thus, making the ring a bit more reserved and more universal. It is this very quality that will allow you to pair this stunning wearable sculpture accessory with more of your favorite looks.</p>
<p>Francoise Oz rings are exclusives that come in only one ring size, listed below. We highly recommend you to consider <a href="http://www.ringsizes.co/info.html" target="_blank">the factors outlined here</a> when determining your ring size, as well as consulting this <a href="http://www.ringsizes.co/" target="_blank">excellent ring size conversion chart</a>. If you need help determining your ring size, contact us through the chat app on this site.</p>
<p>[table id=8 /]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic/product/francoise-oz-faience-ring-with-black-glazing-fr02">Francoise Oz Faience Ring with Black Glazing FR02</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This beautiful one-of-a-kind ring is the definition of an original accessory. It has a sense of true presence, which it conveys through its beautiful organic design. One might infer that the design is fantasy-inspired, yet the ring feels very real. This particular example of creativity and craftsmanship is different from its Francoise Oz counterparts, as it is smaller than the rest of its siblings. This makes the ring a bit more reserved and universal. It is this very quality that will allow you to pair this stunning wearable sculpture accessory with more of your favorite looks.</p>
<h4>About Francoise Oz</h4>
<p>Francoise Oz is an exquisite contemporary wearable sculpture brand with an unconventional, contemporary aesthetic. The process of creation of jewelry from faience and clay, employed by Francoise Oz is meticulous and labor-intensive. Francoise Oz&#8217;s wonderful creations are taking shape through forming raw material, firing, then grinding the fired earthenware pieces by hand and glazing. The resulting pieces are stylish, artistic and absolutely unique. No wonder, Francoise Oz&#8217;s faience and ceramic accessories are endorsed by fashion and design connoisseurs worldwide.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic/product/francoise-oz-faience-ring-with-black-glazing-fr02">Francoise Oz Faience Ring with Black Glazing FR02</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Francoise Oz Matte Ceramic Ring with Metallic Flaking FR03</title>
		<link>http://localhost/wpstatic/product/francoise-oz-ceramic-ring-with-metallic-flaking-fr03</link>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2016 23:44:02 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onewithclouds]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/wpstatic/?post_type=product&#038;p=402</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>This beautiful one-of-a-kind ring is the definition of an original accessory. It has a sense of true presence, which it conveys through its beautifully organic design. One might infer that the design is fantasy-inspired, yet the ring is very real. This particular example of Francoise Oz creativity and craftsmanship is a larger type of ring. It is also special in a way that it's incredible non-glazed ceramics include a myriad of metallic flakes. Also, from a certain angle you can clearly see it as resembling a teddy bear. Overall, this stunning accessory is giving off a spectacular wearable sculpture vibe.</p>
<p>Francoise Oz rings are exclusives that come in only one ring size, listed below. We highly recommend you to consider <a href="http://www.ringsizes.co/info.html" target="_blank">the factors outlined here</a> when determining your ring size, as well as consulting this <a href="http://www.ringsizes.co/" target="_blank">excellent ring size conversion chart</a>. If you need help determining your ring size, contact us through the chat app on this site.</p>
<p>[table id=7 /]</p>
<p>&#160;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic/product/francoise-oz-ceramic-ring-with-metallic-flaking-fr03">Francoise Oz Matte Ceramic Ring with Metallic Flaking FR03</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This beautiful one-of-a-kind ring is the definition of an original accessory. It has a sense of true presence, which it conveys through its beautiful organic design. One might infer that the design is fantasy-inspired, yet the ring feels very real. This particular example of Francoise Oz creativity and craftsmanship is a larger type of ring. It is also special in a way that it&#8217;s incredible non-glazed ceramics include a myriad of metallic flakes. Also, from a certain angle you can clearly see it as resembling a teddy bear. Overall, this stunning accessory is giving off a spectacular wearable sculpture vibe.</p>
<h4>About Francoise Oz</h4>
<p>Francoise Oz is an exquisite contemporary wearable sculpture brand with an unconventional, contemporary aesthetic. The process of creation of jewelry from faience and clay, employed by Francoise Oz is meticulous and labor-intensive. Francoise Oz&#8217;s wonderful creations are taking shape through forming raw material, firing, then grinding the fired earthenware pieces by hand and glazing. The resulting pieces are stylish, artistic and absolutely unique. No wonder, Francoise Oz&#8217;s faience and ceramic accessories are endorsed by fashion and design connoisseurs worldwide.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic/product/francoise-oz-ceramic-ring-with-metallic-flaking-fr03">Francoise Oz Matte Ceramic Ring with Metallic Flaking FR03</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>WooDoo African Blackwood Ring W07</title>
		<link>http://localhost/wpstatic/product/woodoo-african-blackwood-ring-w07</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2016 17:41:06 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onewithclouds]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/wpstatic/?post_type=product&#038;p=243</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>This ring by WooDoo is an incredible piece of contemporary jewelry crafted from extremely rare, and valuable wood. It is an artistic exploration of space that is a creative inquiry into the elegance of spatial geometry. This metaphysical inquiry is skilfully embodied in tactile and precious African Blackwood. As such, it manifests a fluent connection between the worlds of physical-tangible and ethereal-creative. This unique ring has a sense of presence and style that is easily recognizable and truly memorable.</p>
<p>Ring sizes specified in the table below are available in stock and are ready to ship immediately. You can specify your size in the Order Notes field on the Checkout page or we shall contact you for details. Otherwise, please allow up to 5 business days for the creation of your custom ring. We also highly recommend you to consider <a href="http://www.ringsizes.co/info.html" target="_blank">the factors outlined here</a> when determining your ring size, as well as consulting this <a href="http://www.ringsizes.co/" target="_blank">excellent ring size conversion chart</a>. If you need help determining your ring size, contact us through the chat app on this site.</p>
<p>[table id=1 /]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic/product/woodoo-african-blackwood-ring-w07">WooDoo African Blackwood Ring W07</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This ring by WooDoo is an incredible piece of contemporary jewelry crafted from extremely rare, and valuable wood. It is an artistic exploration of space that is a creative inquiry into the elegance of spatial geometry. This metaphysical inquiry is skilfully embodied in tactile and precious African Blackwood. As such, it manifests a fluent connection between the worlds of physical-tangible and ethereal-creative. This unique ring has a sense of presence and style that is easily recognizable and truly memorable.</p>
<h4>Materials</h4>
<p>African Blackwood is a very rare and expensive wood, exhibiting moisture repellent qualities, as well as incredible dimensional stability. This precious wood is highly valued since the ancient times, when its primary usage purposes included furniture and musical instruments. Considered the original ebony thousand of years ago, this wood was imported to and processed in Ancient Egypt. The name &#8220;ebony&#8217; is actually derived from Egyptian &#8220;hbny&#8221;, while other names for this wood include babanus, grenadilla and mpingo. The African Blackwood tree itself takes about 60 years to mature and originates from seasonally dry regions of Senegal, as well as similar regions east to Eritrea and south to Transvaal.</p>
<p>African Blackwood is a lustrous wood that is one of the hardest and densest in the world.  The color hue of African Blackwood ranges from reddish dark brown and purple to pure black. This timber exhibits little or no straight grain and has an even texture. Extremely durable in terms of resistance to decay, African Blackwood is also moderately resistant to insect attacks. While beautiful and durable, this precious wood is notorious for its blunting effect on wood cutters, making it very difficult to work with either by hand or with machine tools. Although pretty much indiscernible upon completion, African Blackwood has a mild distinctive scent that it emits while being processed. Among many precious woods, African Blackwood is considered one of the very finest timbers to be used in producing turned wood objects.</p>
<h4>About WooDoo</h4>
<p>WooDoo is an extraordinary, magnetic, and minimalist jewelry brand. WooDoo is about creative exploration of space and its geometric properties. WooDoo&#8217;s quest is an inquiry into the possibilities of tangible expression of this visionary aesthetic. This brand&#8217;s jewelry transcends the realm of physical, bridging the tangible and the creative.</p>
<p>WooDoo pieces are majestic and truly memorable, while being handcrafted from a number of select precious woods, including African Blackwood, Bog Oak or Purpleheart Wood. Each of the brand&#8217;s pieces is an original and unique experience of jewelry aesthetic. It is this aesthetic, along with skillful execution that WooDoo&#8217;s accessories owe to the duo of creative designers standing behind this visionary brand.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic/product/woodoo-african-blackwood-ring-w07">WooDoo African Blackwood Ring W07</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>WooDoo African Blackwood Ring W08</title>
		<link>http://localhost/wpstatic/product/woodoo-african-blackwood-ring-polyhedral-w08</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2016 13:05:40 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onewithclouds]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/wpstatic/?post_type=product&#038;p=258</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>This ring by WooDoo is an incredible piece of contemporary jewelry crafted from extremely rare, and valuable wood. It is an artistic exploration of space that is a creative inquiry into the elegance of spatial geometry. This metaphysical inquiry is skilfully embodied in tactile and precious African Blackwood. As such, it manifests a fluent connection between the worlds of physical-tangible and ethereal-creative. This unique ring has a sense of presence and style that is easily recognizable and truly memorable.</p>
<p>Ring sizes specified in the table below are available in stock and are ready to ship immediately. You can specify your size in the Order Notes field on the Checkout page or we shall contact you for details. Otherwise, please allow up to 5 business days for the creation of your custom ring. We also highly recommend you to consider <a href="http://www.ringsizes.co/info.html" target="_blank">the factors outlined here</a> when determining your ring size, as well as consulting this <a href="http://www.ringsizes.co/" target="_blank">excellent ring size conversion chart</a>. If you need help determining your ring size, contact us through the chat app on this site.</p>
<p>[table id=2 /]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic/product/woodoo-african-blackwood-ring-polyhedral-w08">WooDoo African Blackwood Ring W08</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This ring by WooDoo is an incredible piece of contemporary jewelry crafted from extremely rare, and valuable wood. It is an artistic exploration of space that is a creative inquiry into the elegance of spatial geometry. This metaphysical inquiry is skilfully embodied in tactile and precious African Blackwood. As such, it manifests a fluent connection between the worlds of physical-tangible and ethereal-creative. This unique ring has a sense of presence and style that is easily recognizable and truly memorable.</p>
<h4>Materials</h4>
<p>African Blackwood is a very rare and expensive wood, exhibiting moisture repellent qualities, as well as incredible dimensional stability. This precious wood is highly valued since the ancient times, when its primary usage purposes included furniture and musical instruments. Considered the original ebony thousand of years ago, this wood was imported to and processed in Ancient Egypt. The name &#8220;ebony&#8217; is actually derived from Egyptian &#8220;hbny&#8221;, while other names for this wood include babanus, grenadilla and mpingo. The African Blackwood tree itself takes about 60 years to mature and originates from seasonally dry regions of Senegal, as well as similar regions east to Eritrea and south to Transvaal.</p>
<p>African Blackwood is a lustrous wood that is one of the hardest and densest in the world.  The color hue of African Blackwood ranges from reddish dark brown and purple to pure black. This timber exhibits little or no straight grain and has an even texture. Extremely durable in terms of resistance to decay, African Blackwood is also moderately resistant to insect attacks. While beautiful and durable, this precious wood is notorious for its blunting effect on wood cutters, making it very difficult to work with either by hand or with machine tools. Although pretty much indiscernible upon completion, African Blackwood has a mild distinctive scent that it emits while being processed. Among many precious woods, African Blackwood is considered one of the very finest timbers to be used in producing turned wood objects.</p>
<h4>About WooDoo</h4>
<p>WooDoo is an extraordinary, magnetic, and minimalist jewelry brand. WooDoo is about creative exploration of space and its geometric properties. WooDoo&#8217;s quest is an inquiry into the possibilities of tangible expression of this visionary aesthetic. This brand&#8217;s jewelry transcends the realm of physical, bridging the tangible and the creative.</p>
<p>WooDoo pieces are majestic and truly memorable, while being handcrafted from a number of select precious woods, including African Blackwood, Bog Oak or Purpleheart Wood. Each of the brand&#8217;s pieces is an original and unique experience of jewelry aesthetic. It is this aesthetic, along with skillful execution that WooDoo&#8217;s accessories owe to the duo of creative designers standing behind this visionary brand.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic/product/woodoo-african-blackwood-ring-polyhedral-w08">WooDoo African Blackwood Ring W08</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>WooDoo Deer Antler Ring W09</title>
		<link>http://localhost/wpstatic/product/woodoo-dear-antler-ring-textured-w09</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2016 13:28:58 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onewithclouds]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/wpstatic/?post_type=product&#038;p=267</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>This deer antler ring is created to showcase the beauty and finesse of a natural material historically used in jewelry-making for tens of thousands of years. Polished deer antlers boast a great palette of original color shades, complemented by an authentic texture and a unique tactile feel that seems different, but somehow familiar at the same time. An original idea for a rustic designer ring, this accessory may  be considered a tribute to some of the earliest man-made jewelry, as well as poetic, yet raw beauty of nature. Being larger in size, the ring stands out with a flare of natural colors and unique tactile feel, as well as a unique patch of unpolished antler texture on the upper of the ring.</p>
<p>Ring sizes specified in the table below are available in stock and are ready to ship immediately. You can specify your size in the Order Notes field on the Checkout page or we shall contact you for details. Otherwise, please allow up to 5 business days for the creation of your custom ring. We also highly recommend you to consider <a href="http://www.ringsizes.co/info.html" target="_blank">the factors outlined here</a> when determining your ring size, as well as consulting this <a href="http://www.ringsizes.co/" target="_blank">excellent ring size conversion chart</a>. If you need help determining your ring size, contact us through the chat app on this site.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic/product/woodoo-dear-antler-ring-textured-w09">WooDoo Deer Antler Ring W09</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This deer antler ring is created to showcase the beauty and finesse of a natural material historically used in jewelry-making for tens of thousands of years. Deer antlers boast a great palette of original color shades, complemented by an authentic texture and a unique tactile feel that seems different, but somehow familiar at the same time. An original idea for a rustic designer ring, this accessory may  be considered a tribute to some of the earliest man-made jewelry, as well as poetic, yet raw beauty of nature. Being larger in size, the ring stands out with a flare of natural colors and unique tactile feel, as well as a unique patch of unpolished antler texture on the upper of the ring.</p>
<h4>Materials</h4>
<p>Antlers are extensions of the skull, seasonally grown and shed by members of the deer family. Antlers are true bone that grows symmetrically in pairs and are mostly attributable to males. The growth of these unique structures places a considerable nutritional strain on the body of a deer. The size of antlers speaks of a deer&#8217;s ability to navigate and find enough food in its environment. Since the prehistoric times antlers were used to make tools, weapons and jewelry. Some antlers have unique properties, as is the case with moose antlers that greatly aid a moose&#8217;s hearing. Antlers are well known for their use by Magdalenian culture in European Late Paleolithic. From this culture, modern museums inherited a number of beautifully carved and engraved pieces of prehistoric art, including this &#8216;<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bison_Licking_Insect_Bite" target="_blank">Bison Licking Insect Bite</a>&#8216; spear-thrower fragment created sometime between 10,000 &#8211; 18,000 BC.</p>
<h4>About WooDoo</h4>
<p>WooDoo is an extraordinary, magnetic, and minimalist jewelry brand. WooDoo is about creative exploration of space and its geometric properties. WooDoo&#8217;s quest is an inquiry into the possibilities of tangible expression of this visionary aesthetic. This brand&#8217;s jewelry transcends the realm of physical, bridging the tangible and the creative.</p>
<p>WooDoo pieces are majestic and truly memorable, while being handcrafted from a number of select precious woods, including African Blackwood, Bog Oak or Purpleheart Wood. Each of the brand&#8217;s pieces is an original and unique experience of jewelry aesthetic. It is this aesthetic, along with skillful execution that WooDoo&#8217;s accessories owe to the duo of creative designers standing behind this visionary brand.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic/product/woodoo-dear-antler-ring-textured-w09">WooDoo Deer Antler Ring W09</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>WooDoo Deer Antler Ring W10</title>
		<link>http://localhost/wpstatic/product/woodoo-deer-antler-ring-polished-w10</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2016 13:35:19 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onewithclouds]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/wpstatic/?post_type=product&#038;p=272</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>This deer antler ring is created to showcase the beauty and finesse of a natural material historically used in jewelry-making for tens of thousands of years. Polished deer antlers boast a great palette of original color shades, complemented by an authentic texture and a unique tactile feel that seems different, but somehow familiar at the same time. The resulting polished deer antler ring in this case is understated and casual. Its tactile feel is pleasant and has an unexpected warmth to it. The texture surface is mostly smooth, while interesting small variations in pattern and color can be discovered upon a more careful examination. This original ring has prominent casual appeal, feeling so comfortable you might want to wear it every day.</p>
<p>Ring sizes specified in the table below are available in stock and are ready to ship immediately. You can specify your size in the Order Notes field on the Checkout page or we shall contact you for details. Otherwise, please allow up to 5 business days for the creation of your custom ring. We also highly recommend you to consider <a href="http://www.ringsizes.co/info.html" target="_blank">the factors outlined here</a> when determining your ring size, as well as consulting this <a href="http://www.ringsizes.co/" target="_blank">excellent ring size conversion chart</a>. If you need help determining your ring size, contact us through the chat app on this site.</p>
<p>[table id=5 /]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic/product/woodoo-deer-antler-ring-polished-w10">WooDoo Deer Antler Ring W10</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This deer antler ring is created to showcase the beauty and finesse of a natural material historically used in jewelry-making for tens of thousands of years. Polished deer antlers boast a great palette of original color shades, complemented by an authentic texture and a unique tactile feel that seems different, but somehow familiar at the same time. The resulting polished deer antler ring in this case is understated and casual. Its tactile feel is pleasant and has an unexpected warmth to it. The texture surface is mostly smooth, while interesting small variations in pattern and color can be discovered upon a more careful examination. This original ring has prominent casual appeal, feeling so comfortable you might want to wear it every day.</p>
<h4>Materials</h4>
<p>Antlers are extensions of the skull, seasonally grown and shed by members of the deer family. Antlers are true bone that grows symmetrically in pairs and are mostly attributable to males. The growth of these unique structures places a considerable nutritional strain on the body of a deer. The size of antlers speaks of a deer&#8217;s ability to navigate and find enough food in its environment. Since the prehistoric times antlers were used to make tools, weapons and jewelry. Some antlers have unique properties, as is the case with moose antlers that greatly aid a moose&#8217;s hearing. Antlers are well known for their use by Magdalenian culture in European Late Paleolithic. From this culture, modern museums inherited a number of beautifully carved and engraved pieces of prehistoric art, including this &#8216;<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bison_Licking_Insect_Bite" target="_blank">Bison Licking Insect Bite</a>&#8216; spear-thrower fragment created sometime between 10,000 &#8211; 18,000 BC.</p>
<h4>About WooDoo</h4>
<p>WooDoo is an extraordinary, magnetic, and minimalist jewelry brand. WooDoo is about creative exploration of space and its geometric properties. WooDoo&#8217;s quest is an inquiry into the possibilities of tangible expression of this visionary aesthetic. This brand&#8217;s jewelry transcends the realm of physical, bridging the tangible and the creative.</p>
<p>WooDoo pieces are majestic and truly memorable, while being handcrafted from a number of select precious woods, including African Blackwood, Bog Oak or Purpleheart Wood. Each of the brand&#8217;s pieces is an original and unique experience of jewelry aesthetic. It is this aesthetic, along with skillful execution that WooDoo&#8217;s accessories owe to the duo of creative designers standing behind this visionary brand.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic/product/woodoo-deer-antler-ring-polished-w10">WooDoo Deer Antler Ring W10</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>WooDoo Hybrid Acrylic-Wood Ring W03</title>
		<link>http://localhost/wpstatic/product/woodoo-acrylicwood-hybrid-ring-w03</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2016 16:28:51 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onewithclouds]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/wpstatic/?post_type=product&#038;p=224</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>This larger ring by WooDoo is a great piece of contemporary jewelry created from unique and modern acrylic-wood hybrid. It is an artistic exploration of space that is a creative inquiry into the elegance of spatial geometry. This inquiry is skilfully embodied in exceptionally aesthetic acrylic-wood hybrid. As such, it manifests a fluent connection between the worlds of physical-tangible and ethereal-creative. This unique ring has a sense of presence and style that is easily recognizable and truly memorable.</p>
<p>You can specify your ring size in the Order Notes field on the Checkout page. Otherwise, we shall contact you for details. Please allow up to 5 business days for the creation of your custom ring. We also highly recommend you to consider <a href="http://www.ringsizes.co/info.html" target="_blank">the factors outlined here</a> when determining your ring size, as well as consulting this <a href="http://www.ringsizes.co/" target="_blank">excellent ring size conversion chart</a>. If you need help determining your ring size, contact us through the chat app on this site.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic/product/woodoo-acrylicwood-hybrid-ring-w03">WooDoo Hybrid Acrylic-Wood Ring W03</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This larger ring by WooDoo is a great piece of contemporary jewelry created from unique and modern acrylic-wood hybrid. It is an artistic exploration of space that is a creative inquiry into the elegance of spatial geometry. This inquiry is skilfully embodied in exceptionally aesthetic acrylic-wood hybrid. As such, it manifests a fluent connection between the worlds of physical-tangible and ethereal-creative. This unique ring has a sense of presence and style that is easily recognizable and truly memorable.</p>
<h4>Materials</h4>
<p>Hybrid wood is a uniquely aesthetic, modern material that builds upon reclaiming highly figured, fragile and incomplete wood. Through a process of stabilization, a vacuum is used to remove all the air from the wood, replacing it with heat activated polymer resin. Once completely infused with the stabilizing solution the wood-acrylic blocks are cast and heat cured, creating a polymer backbone in otherwise fragile pieces. Upon penetration acrylic resin colors the wood, while usually contrasting with it. The polymer resin is also often used to emphasize beautiful grain of the stabilized wood. The resulting wood-acrylic hybrids are extremely durable and will neither exhibit further color shifts, nor absorb any moisture.</p>
<p>The process of creating hybrid wood relies heavily on reclaiming, up-cycling and saving fragile or otherwise unusable wood. The properties of resulting wood-acrylic hybrid resemble that of a dense hardwood, serving as durable and stunning basis for show-stopping pieces. These pieces are developed with traditional woodworking techniques through cutting, shaping and sanding.</p>
<h4>About WooDoo</h4>
<p>WooDoo is an extraordinary, magnetic, and minimalist jewelry brand. WooDoo is about creative exploration of space and its geometric properties. WooDoo&#8217;s quest is an inquiry into the possibilities of tangible expression of this visionary aesthetic. This brand&#8217;s jewelry transcends the realm of physical, bridging the tangible and the creative.</p>
<p>WooDoo pieces are majestic and truly memorable, while being handcrafted from a number of select precious woods, including African Blackwood, Bog Oak or Purpleheart Wood. Each of the brand&#8217;s pieces is an original and unique experience of jewelry aesthetic. It is this aesthetic, along with skillful execution that WooDoo&#8217;s accessories owe to the duo of creative designers standing behind this visionary brand.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic/product/woodoo-acrylicwood-hybrid-ring-w03">WooDoo Hybrid Acrylic-Wood Ring W03</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>WooDoo Purpleheart Wood Ring W01</title>
		<link>http://localhost/wpstatic/product/woodoo-dihedral-ring-from-purpleheart-wood-w01</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2016 15:36:34 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onewithclouds]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/wpstatic/?post_type=product&#038;p=211</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>This ring by WooDoo is an incredible piece of contemporary jewelry crafted from extremely rare, and valuable wood. It is an artistic exploration of space that is a creative inquiry into the elegance of spatial geometry. This metaphysical inquiry is skilfully embodied in tactile and precious Purpleheart wood. As such, it manifests a fluent connection between the worlds of physical-tangible and ethereal-creative. This unique ring has a sense of presence and style that is easily recognizable and truly memorable.</p>
<p>Ring sizes specified in the table below are available in stock and are ready to ship immediately. You can specify your size in the Order Notes field on the Checkout page or we shall contact you for details. Otherwise, please allow up to 5 business days for the creation of your custom ring. We also highly recommend you to consider <a href="http://www.ringsizes.co/info.html" target="_blank">the factors outlined here</a> when determining your ring size, as well as consulting this <a href="http://www.ringsizes.co/" target="_blank">excellent ring size conversion chart</a>. If you need help determining your ring size, contact us through the chat app on this site.</p>
<p>[table id=4 /]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic/product/woodoo-dihedral-ring-from-purpleheart-wood-w01">WooDoo Purpleheart Wood Ring W01</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This ring by WooDoo is an incredible piece of contemporary jewelry crafted from extremely rare, and valuable wood. It is an artistic exploration of space that is a creative inquiry into the elegance of spatial geometry. This metaphysical inquiry is skilfully embodied in tactile and precious Purpleheart wood. As such, it manifests a fluent connection between the worlds of physical-tangible and ethereal-creative. This unique ring has a sense of presence and style that is easily recognizable and truly memorable.</p>
<h4>Materials</h4>
<p>Purpleheart is a unique precious wood that originates from the Pacific Coast of Panama and Costa Rica, as well as Atlantic Coast of Colombia. Growing up to 50m in height Purpleheart trees produce a hard and durable wood that is nevertheless notoriously difficult to work with. This difficulty stems from the wood&#8217;s tendency to release a gummy resin, when heated with dull tools or if cutter speeds are too high. The heartwood of Purpleheart is dull brown upon cutting, transforming to a shade of purple upon exposure to UV light. With aging and further exposure to UV, the Purpleheart wood will gradually shift color to dark brown with a touch of its signature purple. This transformation can be slowed by applying a UV inhibiting coating.</p>
<p>Being quite dense, purple heart is also water-resistant. This wood is very durable, and is not susceptible to decay or most of the insect attacks. The grain of this wood is mostly straight but can be wavy or irregular, while the texture is medium and exhibits a great natural luster. As to this wood&#8217;s metaphysical properties, it is believed that it can enhance creativity, facilitate acquisition of new knowledge, as well as healing and good health.</p>
<h4>About WooDoo</h4>
<p>WooDoo is an extraordinary, magnetic, and minimalist jewelry brand. WooDoo is about creative exploration of space and its geometric properties. WooDoo&#8217;s quest is an inquiry into the possibilities of tangible expression of this visionary aesthetic. This brand&#8217;s jewelry transcends the realm of physical, bridging the tangible and the creative.</p>
<p>WooDoo pieces are majestic and truly memorable, while being handcrafted from a number of select precious woods, including African Blackwood, Bog Oak or Purpleheart Wood. Each of the brand&#8217;s pieces is an original and unique experience of jewelry aesthetic. It is this aesthetic, along with skillful execution that WooDoo&#8217;s accessories owe to the duo of creative designers standing behind this visionary brand.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic/product/woodoo-dihedral-ring-from-purpleheart-wood-w01">WooDoo Purpleheart Wood Ring W01</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>WooDoo Purpleheart Wood Ring W02</title>
		<link>http://localhost/wpstatic/product/woodoo-purpleheart-wood-ring-w02</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2016 15:59:19 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onewithclouds]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/wpstatic/?post_type=product&#038;p=218</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>This ring by WooDoo is an incredible piece of contemporary jewelry crafted from extremely rare, and valuable wood. It is an artistic exploration of space that is a creative inquiry into the elegance of spatial geometry. This metaphysical inquiry is skilfully embodied in tactile and precious Purpleheart wood. As such, it manifests a fluent connection between the worlds of physical-tangible and ethereal-creative. This unique ring has a sense of presence and style that is easily recognizable and truly memorable.</p>
<p>Ring sizes specified in the table below are available in stock and are ready to ship immediately. You can specify your size in the Order Notes field on the Checkout page or we shall contact you for details. Otherwise, please allow up to 5 business days for the creation of your custom ring. We also highly recommend you to consider <a href="http://www.ringsizes.co/info.html" target="_blank">the factors outlined here</a> when determining your ring size, as well as consulting this <a href="http://www.ringsizes.co/" target="_blank">excellent ring size conversion chart</a>. If you need help determining your ring size, contact us through the chat app on this site.</p>
<p>[table id=3 /]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic/product/woodoo-purpleheart-wood-ring-w02">WooDoo Purpleheart Wood Ring W02</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This ring by WooDoo is an incredible piece of contemporary jewelry crafted from extremely rare, and valuable wood. It is an artistic exploration of space that is a creative inquiry into the elegance of spatial geometry. This metaphysical inquiry is skilfully embodied in tactile and precious Purpleheart wood. As such, it manifests a fluent connection between the worlds of physical-tangible and ethereal-creative. This unique ring has a sense of presence and style that is easily recognizable and truly memorable.</p>
<h4>Materials</h4>
<p>Purpleheart is a unique precious wood that originates from the Pacific Coast of Panama and Costa Rica, as well as Atlantic Coast of Colombia. Growing up to 50m in height Purpleheart trees produce a hard and durable wood that is nevertheless notoriously difficult to work with. This difficulty stems from the wood&#8217;s tendency to release a gummy resin, when heated with dull tools or if cutter speeds are too high. The heartwood of Purpleheart is dull brown upon cutting, transforming to a shade of purple upon exposure to UV light. With aging and further exposure to UV, the Purpleheart wood will gradually shift color to dark brown with a touch of its signature purple. This transformation can be slowed by applying a UV inhibiting coating.</p>
<p>Being quite dense, purple heart is also water-resistant. This wood is very durable, and is not susceptible to decay or most of the insect attacks. The grain of this wood is mostly straight but can be wavy or irregular, while the texture is medium and exhibits a great natural luster. As to this wood&#8217;s metaphysical properties, it is believed that it can enhance creativity, facilitate acquisition of new knowledge, as well as healing and good health.</p>
<h4>About WooDoo</h4>
<p>WooDoo is an incredibly magnetic contemporary jewelry brand unlike any other. WooDoo is concerned with creative exploration of space, its geometric properties, as well as the possibilities of their tangible expression. All of this combines into a very original and unique aesthetic. WooDoo&#8217;s works are true artistic explorations of the properties of space. These explorations stem from visions of space that get translated into the physical world by means of minimalist tangible objects. But even after receiving physical form, WooDoo&#8217;s jewelry pieces feel deeply rooted in the realm of creative and visionary.</p>
<p>WooDoo&#8217;s accessories are truly memorable, commanding attention and recognition and are handcrafted from a number of select tactile precious woods, like African Blackwood or Purpleheart Wood. Each of WooDoo&#8217;s jewelry pieces carries an unmistakably modern, contemporary jewelry aesthetic. It is this aesthetic, along with skillful execution that WooDoo&#8217;s accessories owe to the duo of creative designers, standing behind this unique and visionary brand.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic/product/woodoo-purpleheart-wood-ring-w02">WooDoo Purpleheart Wood Ring W02</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
