<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>floral print &#8211; Nuage Showroom</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/wpstatic/product-tag/floral-print/feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://localhost/wpstatic</link>
	<description>Our Clothing &#38; Accessories</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 01:55:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>WooDoo Bog Oak Bracelet with Floral Print W05</title>
		<link>http://localhost/wpstatic/product/woodoo-bog-oak-and-leather-bracelet-with-golden-floral-print-w05</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2016 17:24:31 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onewithclouds]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/wpstatic/?post_type=product&#038;p=240</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>A conceptual piece this bracelet is made with extremely rare and valuable bog oak. The look of the centerpiece on a minimalist leather strap mimics that of a watch, except the watch-face is replaced with a print. This golden floral print stands out elegantly, adding some welcome warmth to the all black color scheme. The aesthetics of bog oak, which takes thousands of years to mature, hint at the balance of endurance and change in the face of passing time. This concept is contrasted with a warm and inviting golden floral print that can be seen to symbolize nature. Skillfully crafted, this bracelet is a stunning contemporary piece that is minimalist, creative and unique.</p>
<p>Bog Oak is an exceptionally rare form of timber that is comparable to some of the most expensive tropical hardwoods. It is notable for high strength and magnificent beauty. Other common names of bog-wood include abanos and morta. Essentially, bog oak is oak wood in the early stages of fossilization. This type of wood cannot be produced artificially, so it can only be obtained from natural sources like peat bogs and river beds. Having been submerged in acidic, oxygen-free conditions, this type of wood takes literally hundreds, but more often thousands of years to "mature". During this time iron and minerals from the water bind with tannin in the wood, resulting in a considerably darker, golden-brown to pure black color, as well as a significantly increased hardness and density. Due to this density, bog oak can only be carved with exceptionally firm tools.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic/product/woodoo-bog-oak-and-leather-bracelet-with-golden-floral-print-w05">WooDoo Bog Oak Bracelet with Floral Print W05</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A conceptual piece, this bracelet is made with extremely rare and valuable bog oak. The look of the centerpiece on a minimalist leather strap mimics that of a watch, except the watch-face is replaced with a print. This golden floral print stands out elegantly, adding some welcome warmth to the all black color scheme. The aesthetics of bog oak, which takes thousands of years to mature, hint at the endurance, change and immensity of passing time. This concept is contrasted with a warm and inviting golden floral print that can be seen to symbolize nature. Skillfully crafted, this bracelet is a stunning contemporary piece that is minimalist, creative and unique.</p>
<h4>Materials</h4>
<p>Bog Oak is an exceptionally rare form of timber that is comparable to some of the most expensive tropical hardwoods. It is notable for high strength and magnificent beauty. Other common names of bog-wood include abanos and morta. Essentially, bog oak is oak wood in the early stages of fossilization. This type of wood cannot be produced artificially, so it can only be obtained from natural sources like peat bogs and river beds. Having been submerged in acidic, oxygen-free conditions, this type of wood takes literally hundreds, but more often thousands of years to &#8220;mature&#8221;. During this time iron and minerals from the water bind with tannin in the wood, resulting in a considerably darker, golden-brown to pure black color, as well as a significantly increased hardness and density. Due to this density, bog oak can only be carved with exceptionally firm tools.</p>
<p>Since supply of bog oak is so limited, prices for this type of wood are quite high. This is attributable to the fact that sites of bog oak are extremely rare and hard to access. The recovery of bog-wood trunks is often a difficult and engaging process, requiring meticulous preparation. At the same time, the much anticipated moment of extraction is the wood&#8217;s first exposure to light in hundreds and thousands of years. Extracted bog-wood is very delicate and requires complex desiccation. Nevertheless, despite great care most of the raw wood is not suitable for processing. Processing itself is notoriously unpredictable as some parts may be supple, while others very hard. All of this implies high value of raw and processed bog-oak wood.</p>
<p>From the viewpoint of aesthetics, bog-oak is a genuine experience of naturally formed color. This is particularly appealing to material connoisseurs who point to exquisite permeation of wood structure by the dark and noble color. The authenticity of this wood is complemented by its texture and grain. Parts of the wood may become combined, creating variations in color, as well as direction of growth rings. This imperfect appearance often adds to the aesthetic of bog-wood, conveying a powerful message of intensity of the past times, as well as longevity of the wood and the fact of its remaining intact. It may very well be the reason why in the nineteenth century bog oak was used to make exceptionally beautiful carved decorative jewelry.</p>
<p>As to the symbolism and metaphysical properties associated with the materials used in this bracelet, oak is one of the most sacred trees that stands for the invocation of wisdom, authority, endurance, strength and protection. Oak is also believed to bring vitality and long life and is considered among the most powerful and sacred Druid woods. In Ancient Celtic culture oak was considered to be the protector. Oak wood is also used as healing wood and is believed to aid in focusing the mind on the task at hand. Oak is said to inspire bravery, presence, leadership and enduring strength.</p>
<h4>About WooDoo</h4>
<p>WooDoo is an incredibly magnetic contemporary jewelry brand unlike any other. WooDoo is concerned with creative exploration of space, its geometric properties, as well as the possibilities of their tangible expression. All of this combines into a very original and unique aesthetic. WooDoo&#8217;s works are true artistic explorations of the properties of space. These explorations stem from visions of space that get translated into the physical world by means of minimalist tangible objects. But even after receiving physical form, WooDoo&#8217;s jewelry pieces feel deeply rooted in the realm of creative and visionary.</p>
<p>WooDoo&#8217;s accessories are truly memorable, commanding attention and recognition and are handcrafted from a number of select tactile precious woods, like African Blackwood or Purpleheart Wood. Each of WooDoo&#8217;s jewelry pieces carries an unmistakably modern, contemporary jewelry aesthetic. It is this aesthetic, along with skillful execution that WooDoo&#8217;s accessories owe to the duo of creative designers, standing behind this unique and visionary brand.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic/product/woodoo-bog-oak-and-leather-bracelet-with-golden-floral-print-w05">WooDoo Bog Oak Bracelet with Floral Print W05</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
