<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>silver plated collar &#8211; Nuage Showroom</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/wpstatic/product-tag/silver-plated-collar/feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://localhost/wpstatic</link>
	<description>Our Clothing &#38; Accessories</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 01:55:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Tsumi Volcanic Rock Necklace TS202</title>
		<link>http://localhost/wpstatic/product/tsumi-necklace-volcanic-lava-ts202</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2016 14:08:39 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onewithclouds]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/wpstatic/product/tsumi-necklace-volcanic-lava-ts202</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>An absolutely gorgeous accessory from the brand's latest collection, this volcanic lava necklace possesses the sophistication and a sense of style to make a truly memorable impression. Created in a silver/black color scheme, this necklace is remarkable for its beautiful detailing and gorgeous design. Skillfully crafted using a number of techniques, this necklace is inspired by the Moon. The highlight of the necklace are the volcanic lava and glass beads, a gracious silver-plated brass collar band, as well as a chain and satin tape. The front drop of this beautiful necklace measures 9cm (3.54").</p>
<p>Materials: Volcanic Rock (Lava Rock), Metal Chains, Glass, Satin Tape, Silver Plated Collar. Front Drop - 9 cm.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic/product/tsumi-necklace-volcanic-lava-ts202">Tsumi Volcanic Rock Necklace TS202</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An absolutely gorgeous accessory from the brand&#8217;s latest collection, this volcanic lava necklace possesses the sophistication and a sense of style to make a truly memorable impression. Created in a silver/black color scheme, this necklace is remarkable for its beautiful detailing and gorgeous design. Skillfully crafted using a number of techniques, this necklace is inspired by the Moon. The highlight of the necklace are the volcanic lava and glass beads, a gracious silver-plated brass collar band, as well as a chain and satin tape. The front drop of this beautiful necklace measures 9cm (3.54&#8243;).</p>
<h4>Materials</h4>
<p>Lava rock, volcanic rock or basalt is a beautiful matte black stone with an incredible texture. It is believed to be an excellent grounding stone, strengthening one&#8217;s connection to Mother Earth and providing stability in the time of change. Lava rock is also often thought of as a physical embodiment of fire, being a stone that started as fiery molten lava, subsequently turning into rock.</p>
<h4>About Tsumi</h4>
<p>Tsumi is a brand born from the love of fashion, as well as an inherent need to be original and unique. Each Tsumi accessory is infused by a touch of authentic ethnic flair and is inspired by joyful memories of traveling the world. Tsumi accessories are crafted with an incredible skill, while remaining visionary and creative pieces of contemporary jewelry.</p>
<p>Most of Tsumi accessories are made in either limited quantity or in one unique specimen. Tsumi is also synonymous with an exceptional selection of original and rare materials used to create their stylish accessories. These include semi-precious stones, corals, pearls and crystals, making Tsumi jewelry not only an embodiment of original style, but also an experience.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic/product/tsumi-necklace-volcanic-lava-ts202">Tsumi Volcanic Rock Necklace TS202</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
