<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>nacre &#8211; Nuage Showroom</title>
	<atom:link href="http://nuage21.com/product-tag/nacre/feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://nuage21.com</link>
	<description>Our Clothing &#38; Accessories</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 01:55:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Miracle Princess Necklace with Nacre and Agate M05</title>
		<link>http://nuage21.com/product/miracle-princess-necklace-with-nacre-and-agate-m05</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 10:07:43 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onewithclouds]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://nuage21.com/?post_type=product&#038;p=334</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>A stunning Miracle necklace, the Princess pays a tribute to jewelry traditions with a sophisticated and fashionable, yet modern design. Incredibly stylish, subtle and elegant, this necklace is impressive with its detailing and is carrying an unmistakable sense of presence and refinement. An apt selection of materials for this necklace includes agate, mother of pearl (nacre), howlite and reps ribbon. One might infer with absolute confidence that this necklace will favorably complement a number of your fashionable looks.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://nuage21.com/product/miracle-princess-necklace-with-nacre-and-agate-m05">Miracle Princess Necklace with Nacre and Agate M05</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://nuage21.com">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A stunning Miracle necklace, the Princess pays a tribute to jewelry traditions with a sophisticated and fashionable, yet modern design. Incredibly stylish, subtle and elegant, this necklace is impressive with its detailing and is carrying an unmistakable sense of presence and refinement. An apt selection of materials for this necklace includes agate, mother of pearl (nacre), howlite and reps ribbon. One might infer with absolute confidence that this necklace will favorably complement a number of your fashionable looks.</p>
<h4>Materials</h4>
<p>Agate is a magnificent  stone that is believed to have been one of humanity&#8217;s earliest possessions. According to researchers, Agate was mined in Ancient Egypt as early as 3500 B.C. As per Agate&#8217;s properties, it is regarded as providing a harmonizing influence. It is believed to help with balancing of emotional, physical and intellectual endeavors, harmonizing the Ying and Yang. A soothing and calming stone, Agate is thought to bring great strength gradually and is said to aid with the acceptances of oneself/building self confidence. It is also believed that Agate can improve concentration and analytical abilities, resulting in newfound practical solutions.</p>
<p>Mother of Pearl (Nacre) has been used in jewelry for thousands of years, with the earliest known pieces attributable to ancient Egyptians and Sumerians. East Asian and Islamic art has also used nacre for beautiful inlay work. Mother of Pearl has become extremely popular in Europe during the Victorian Era. This organic gemstone belongs to a small group that includes coral, amber, jet, ivory and, of course, pearl. Mother of Pearl is often thought of as encouraging prosperity, offering motherly and soothing protection, while promoting intuition and imagination.</p>
<p>Howlite is considered to be a stone of calm and tranquility. A stone that can calm and soothe the emotions, help cope with an overactive mind and achieve a deep and restful sleep. Howlite is believed to reduce conflicts, facilitate communication, promote kindness, compassion and peaceful coexistence.  This truly beautiful and tranquil gem is believed to aid in clarifying one’s mind to develop a more prominent awareness of ambitions and goals. Often referred to as an ‘attunement stone’, Howlite is thought to help expand the horizons and open the mind to wisdom and new knowledge.</p>
<h4>About Miracle</h4>
<p>Miracle is a unique brand that is based in refined, sophisticated and feminine accessories. Accessories that combine a sense of jewelry tradition with notions of elegant, modern and contemporary jewelry. Truly a designer brand, Miracle seems to embody the commitment to a woman&#8217;s passion for outstanding accessories, creating undeniably beautiful pieces, from necklaces to earrings and bracelets. Miracle&#8217;s apt selection of favorite materials includes howlite, quartz, cat&#8217;s eye and agate. Taking a piece of Miracle&#8217;s jewelry into a hand, one can&#8217;t help but acknowledge the brand&#8217;s unmistakable original style that combines true refinement with sensual elegance.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://nuage21.com/product/miracle-princess-necklace-with-nacre-and-agate-m05">Miracle Princess Necklace with Nacre and Agate M05</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://nuage21.com">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
