<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Bracelets &#8211; Nuage Showroom</title>
	<atom:link href="https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product-category/bracelets/feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage</link>
	<description>Our Clothing &#38; Accessories</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2018 02:02:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Miracle Rose Quartz Crystal Bracelet M09</title>
		<link>https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/miracle-rose-quartz-bracelet-m09</link>
		<comments>https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/miracle-rose-quartz-bracelet-m09#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 10:58:02 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onewithclouds]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/?post_type=product&#038;p=347</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>This bracelet is a unique accessory exemplifying Miracle's trademark fusion of historic jewelry tradition with stylistic cues and elegance of modern contemporary jewelry aesthetic. The bracelet is 16.5cm (6.5") long and is based on a larger chain complemented by creatively combined beads that provide tasteful accents to the overall color scheme. The centerpiece of the bracelet is an element of Rose Quartz, a crystal that has always been considered a symbol of unconditional love. This beautiful accessory shares refinement and style that will perfectly complement Miracle's incredible necklaces.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/miracle-rose-quartz-bracelet-m09">Miracle Rose Quartz Crystal Bracelet M09</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This bracelet is a unique accessory exemplifying Miracle&#8217;s trademark fusion of historic jewelry tradition with stylistic cues and elegance of modern contemporary jewelry aesthetic. The bracelet is 16.5cm (6.5&#8243;) long and is based on a larger chain complemented by creatively combined beads that provide tasteful accents to the overall color scheme. The centerpiece of the bracelet is an element of Rose Quartz, a crystal that has always been considered a symbol of unconditional love. This beautiful accessory shares refinement and style that will perfectly complement Miracle&#8217;s incredible necklaces.</p>
<h4>Materials</h4>
<p>Love is one of the most fundamental and powerful forces in the world. At the same time the color of a pink rose is considered an unmistakable symbol of tenderness, romance and love. Could it be the reason why, in the world of semi-precious gemstones natural Rose Quartz is a crystal  of heartfelt unconditional love, femininity, compassion, healing and romance. It is believed that Rose Quartz can unravel the heart&#8217;s deep inner love not only for others, but also for oneself, allowing to rekindle the appreciation of beauty, nature and art. In this way, Rose Quartz can provide a sense of personal fulfillment and contentment, helping to regain the capacity to truly give and receive love from others.  This crystal is also believed to be effective in developing relationships with family and friends, as well as attracting romance and new love.</p>
<h4>About Miracle</h4>
<p>Miracle is a unique brand that is based in refined, sophisticated and feminine accessories. Accessories that combine a sense of jewelry tradition with notions of elegant, modern and contemporary jewelry. Truly a designer brand, Miracle seems to embody the commitment to a woman&#8217;s passion for outstanding accessories, creating undeniably beautiful pieces, from necklaces to earrings and bracelets. Miracle&#8217;s apt selection of favorite materials includes howlite, quartz, cat&#8217;s eye and agate. Taking a piece of Miracle&#8217;s jewelry into a hand, one can&#8217;t help but acknowledge the brand&#8217;s unmistakable original style that combines true refinement with sensual elegance.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/miracle-rose-quartz-bracelet-m09">Miracle Rose Quartz Crystal Bracelet M09</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/miracle-rose-quartz-bracelet-m09/feed</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tsumi Chain-Ring Bracelet with Hematite TS140</title>
		<link>https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/tsumi-chain-ring-bracelet-with-hematite-ts140</link>
		<comments>https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/tsumi-chain-ring-bracelet-with-hematite-ts140#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2016 15:44:18 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onewithclouds]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/?post_type=product&#038;p=74</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Chain-ring bracelet is a unique accessory that is associated with a number of cultures around the world, but most notably with traditional Hindu jewelry. This particular chain-ring bracelet is a modern interpretation of this traditional, elegant and feminine design. An interpretation that is inspired by the notions of protection and armor. The total length of this medium-sized accessory is 18.5cm (7.28"). This bracelet consists of metal elements, a silver-plated chain, as well as a number of elongated hematite beads. It is these shiny beads that set the mood for this unique accessory. At the same time, the original design, monochrome color palette and an impeccable selection of materials allow this chain-ring bracelet to make a truly outstanding and lasting impression.</p>
<p>Materials: Hematite, Metal Elements, Silver Plated Chain, Sterling Silver Logo Charm. Medium length - 18.5 cm (7.28").</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/tsumi-chain-ring-bracelet-with-hematite-ts140">Tsumi Chain-Ring Bracelet with Hematite TS140</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Chain-ring bracelet is a unique accessory that is associated with a number of cultures around the world, but most notably with traditional Hindu jewelry. This particular chain-ring bracelet is a modern interpretation of this traditional, elegant and feminine design. An interpretation that is inspired by the notions of protection and armor. The total length of this medium-sized accessory is 18.5cm (7.28&#8243;). This bracelet consists of metal elements, a silver-plated chain, as well as a number of elongated hematite beads. It is these shiny beads that set the mood for this unique accessory. At the same time, the original design, monochrome color palette and an impeccable selection of materials allow this chain-ring bracelet to make a truly outstanding and lasting impression.</p>
<h4>Materials</h4>
<p>Hematite is one of the prettiest and most unique crystals used in jewelry accessories. This crystal provides a unique combination of shiny charisma, while retaining the ability to remain reserved. It is one of the few magnetic crystals the structure of which is dominated by iron. Hematite is often referred to as a ‘seeker crystal’ that helps one find a new path or approach to gain something you desire, but not yet posses. Hematite crystals are thought to have great grounding and balancing effect, as well as serving to stimulate mind, memory, sometimes evoking deep thought.</p>
<h4>About Tsumi</h4>
<p>Tsumi is a brand born from the love of fashion, as well as an inherent need to be original and unique. Each Tsumi accessory is infused by a touch of authentic ethnic flair and is inspired by joyful memories of traveling the world. Tsumi accessories are crafted with an incredible skill, while remaining visionary and creative pieces of contemporary jewelry.</p>
<p>Most of Tsumi accessories are made in either limited quantity or in one unique specimen. Tsumi is also synonymous with an exceptional selection of original and rare materials used to create their stylish accessories. These include semi-precious stones, corals, pearls and crystals, making Tsumi jewelry not only an embodiment of original style, but also an experience.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/tsumi-chain-ring-bracelet-with-hematite-ts140">Tsumi Chain-Ring Bracelet with Hematite TS140</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/tsumi-chain-ring-bracelet-with-hematite-ts140/feed</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tsumi Hematite and Quartz Crystal Bracelet TS142</title>
		<link>https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/tsumi-hematite-and-mineral-quartz-necklace-ts142</link>
		<comments>https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/tsumi-hematite-and-mineral-quartz-necklace-ts142#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2016 15:30:18 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onewithclouds]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/?post_type=product&#038;p=67</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>This absolutely fabulous bracelet is inspired by the notion of protection and armor. The unrivaled design of this bracelet owes much to designer's bold and authentic creative vision, as well as impeccable and flawless execution. This bracelet is aptly created in monochrome on the premise of minimal design and outstanding selection of materials. The latter seems to give prominence to this bracelet's original composition through hematite beads that encircle and accentuate the bracelet's most refined and interesting detail - a genuine crystal of Quartz.</p>
<p>Materials: Hematite, Quartz, Metal Elements, Sterling Silver Logo Charm. Length - 19.5 cm (7.67").</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/tsumi-hematite-and-mineral-quartz-necklace-ts142">Tsumi Hematite and Quartz Crystal Bracelet TS142</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This absolutely fabulous bracelet is inspired by the notion of protection and armor. The unrivaled design of this bracelet owes much to designer&#8217;s bold and authentic creative vision, as well as impeccable and flawless execution. This bracelet is aptly created in monochrome on the premise of minimal design and outstanding selection of materials. The latter seems to give prominence to this bracelet&#8217;s original composition through hematite beads that encircle and accentuate the bracelet&#8217;s most refined and interesting detail &#8211; a genuine crystal of Quartz.</p>
<h4>Materials</h4>
<p>Quartz Crystals or Rock Crystals are one of the most beautiful and yet most common types of crystal found on the planet. While often referred to as &#8216;clear quartz&#8217;, the crystals can actually range from clear to cloudy to almost completely opaque. The configurations and shapes they occur in are also numerous. Quartz is one of the most universal crystals that is often believed to be able to amplify feelings, emotions, thoughts and positive affirmations. It is also used to enhance the effects of other crystals and minerals it is used with.</p>
<p>Hematite is one of the prettiest and most unique crystals used in jewelry accessories. This crystal provides a unique combination of shiny charisma, while retaining the ability to remain reserved. It is one of the few magnetic crystals the structure of which is dominated by iron. Hematite is often referred to as a ‘seeker crystal’ that helps one find a new path or approach to gain something you desire, but not yet posses. Hematite crystals are thought to have great grounding and balancing effect, as well as serving to stimulate mind, memory, sometimes evoking deep thought.</p>
<p>Materials: Hematite, Quartz, Metal Elements, Sterling Silver Logo Charm. Medium length &#8211; 19.5 cm.</p>
<h4>About Tsumi</h4>
<p>Tsumi is a brand born from the love of fashion, as well as an inherent need to be original and unique. Each Tsumi accessory is infused by a touch of authentic ethnic flair and is inspired by joyful memories of traveling the world. Tsumi accessories are crafted with an incredible skill, while remaining visionary and creative pieces of contemporary jewelry.</p>
<p>Most of Tsumi accessories are made in either limited quantity or in one unique specimen. Tsumi is also synonymous with an exceptional selection of original and rare materials used to create their stylish accessories. These include semi-precious stones, corals, pearls and crystals, making Tsumi jewelry not only an embodiment of original style, but also an experience.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/tsumi-hematite-and-mineral-quartz-necklace-ts142">Tsumi Hematite and Quartz Crystal Bracelet TS142</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/tsumi-hematite-and-mineral-quartz-necklace-ts142/feed</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>WooDoo Bog Oak Bracelet with a Hidden Print W04</title>
		<link>https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/woodoo-bog-oak-leather-bracelet-stealthy-print-w04</link>
		<comments>https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/woodoo-bog-oak-leather-bracelet-stealthy-print-w04#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2016 17:05:56 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onewithclouds]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/?post_type=product&#038;p=235</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>A conceptual piece, this bracelet is made with extremely rare and valuable bog oak. The look of the centerpiece on a minimalist leather strap mimics that of a watch, except the watch-face is replaced with a print. The monochromatic print is only visible from an angle, giving this bracelet a look that is literally timeless, mysterious and elegant. The aesthetics of bog oak, which takes thousands of years to mature, hint at the endurance, change and immensity of passing time. This beautiful and monumental concept is complemented with a print reminiscent of a crystalline structure. Looking at this watch-inspired bracelet is a bit like staring into infinite and eternal space, making the question of 'what time is it?' a bit redundant. Skillfully crafted, this bracelet is a stunning contemporary piece that is minimalist, creative and unique.</p>
<p>Bog Oak is an exceptionally rare form of timber that is comparable to some of the most expensive tropical hardwoods. It is notable for high strength and magnificent beauty. Other common names of bog-wood include abanos and morta. Essentially, bog oak is oak wood in the early stages of fossilization. This type of wood cannot be produced artificially, so it can only be obtained from natural sources like peat bogs and river beds. Having been submerged in acidic, oxygen-free conditions, this type of wood takes literally hundreds, but more often thousands of years to "mature". During this time iron and minerals from the water bind with tannin in the wood, resulting in a considerably darker, golden-brown to pure black color, as well as a significantly increased hardness and density. Due to this density, bog oak can only be carved with exceptionally firm tools.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/woodoo-bog-oak-leather-bracelet-stealthy-print-w04">WooDoo Bog Oak Bracelet with a Hidden Print W04</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div>A conceptual piece, this bracelet is made with extremely rare and valuable bog oak. The look of the centerpiece on a minimalist leather strap mimics that of a watch, except the watch-face is replaced with a print. The monochromatic print is only visible from an angle, giving this bracelet a look that is literally timeless, mysterious and elegant. The aesthetics of bog oak, which takes thousands of years to mature, hint at the endurance, change and immensity of passing time. This beautiful and monumental concept is complemented with a print reminiscent of a crystalline structure. Looking at this watch-inspired bracelet is a bit like staring into infinite and eternal space, making the question of &#8216;What time is it?&#8217; a bit redundant. Skillfully crafted, this bracelet is a stunning contemporary piece that is minimalist, creative and unique.</div>
<h4>Materials</h4>
<p>Bog Oak is an exceptionally rare form of timber that is comparable to some of the most expensive tropical hardwoods. It is notable for high strength and magnificent beauty. Other common names of bog-wood include abanos and morta. Essentially, bog oak is oak wood in the early stages of fossilization. This type of wood cannot be produced artificially, so it can only be obtained from natural sources like peat bogs and river beds. Having been submerged in acidic, oxygen-free conditions, this type of wood takes literally hundreds, but more often thousands of years to &#8220;mature&#8221;. During this time iron and minerals from the water bind with tannin in the wood, resulting in a considerably darker, golden-brown to pure black color, as well as a significantly increased hardness and density. Due to this density, bog oak can only be carved with exceptionally firm tools.</p>
<p>Since supply of bog oak is so limited, prices for this type of wood are quite high. This is attributable to the fact that sites of bog oak are extremely rare and hard to access. The recovery of bog-wood trunks is often a difficult and engaging process, requiring meticulous preparation. At the same time, the much anticipated moment of extraction is the wood&#8217;s first exposure to light in hundreds and thousands of years. Extracted bog-wood is very delicate and requires complex desiccation. Nevertheless, despite great care most of the raw wood is not suitable for processing. Processing itself is notoriously unpredictable as some parts may be supple, while others very hard. All of this implies high value of raw and processed bog-oak wood.</p>
<p>From the viewpoint of aesthetics, bog-oak is a genuine experience of naturally formed color. This is particularly appealing to material connoisseurs who point to exquisite permeation of wood structure by the dark and noble color. The authenticity of this wood is complemented by its texture and grain. Parts of the wood may become combined, creating variations in color, as well as direction of growth rings. This imperfect appearance often adds to the aesthetic of bog-wood, conveying a powerful message of intensity of the past times, as well as longevity of the wood and the fact of its remaining intact. It may very well be the reason why in the nineteenth century bog oak was used to make exceptionally beautiful carved decorative jewelry.</p>
<p>As to the symbolism and metaphysical properties associated with the materials used in this bracelet, oak is one of the most sacred trees that stands for the invocation of wisdom, authority, endurance, strength and protection. Oak is also believed to bring vitality and long life and is considered among the most powerful and sacred Druid woods. In Ancient Celtic culture oak was considered to be the protector. Oak wood is also used as healing wood and is believed to aid in focusing the mind on the task at hand. Oak is said to inspire bravery, presence, leadership and enduring strength.</p>
<h4>About WooDoo</h4>
<p>WooDoo is an incredibly magnetic contemporary jewelry brand unlike any other. WooDoo is concerned with creative exploration of space, its geometric properties, as well as the possibilities of their tangible expression. All of this combines into a very original and unique aesthetic. WooDoo&#8217;s works are true artistic explorations of the properties of space. These explorations stem from visions of space that get translated into the physical world by means of minimalist tangible objects. But even after receiving physical form, WooDoo&#8217;s jewelry pieces feel deeply rooted in the realm of creative and visionary.</p>
<p>WooDoo&#8217;s accessories are truly memorable, commanding attention and recognition and are handcrafted from a number of select tactile precious woods, like African Blackwood or Purpleheart Wood. Each of WooDoo&#8217;s jewelry pieces carries an unmistakably modern, contemporary jewelry aesthetic. It is this aesthetic, along with skillful execution that WooDoo&#8217;s accessories owe to the duo of creative designers, standing behind this unique and visionary brand.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/woodoo-bog-oak-leather-bracelet-stealthy-print-w04">WooDoo Bog Oak Bracelet with a Hidden Print W04</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/woodoo-bog-oak-leather-bracelet-stealthy-print-w04/feed</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>WooDoo Bog Oak Bracelet with Floral Print W05</title>
		<link>https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/woodoo-bog-oak-and-leather-bracelet-with-golden-floral-print-w05</link>
		<comments>https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/woodoo-bog-oak-and-leather-bracelet-with-golden-floral-print-w05#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2016 17:24:31 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onewithclouds]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/?post_type=product&#038;p=240</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>A conceptual piece this bracelet is made with extremely rare and valuable bog oak. The look of the centerpiece on a minimalist leather strap mimics that of a watch, except the watch-face is replaced with a print. This golden floral print stands out elegantly, adding some welcome warmth to the all black color scheme. The aesthetics of bog oak, which takes thousands of years to mature, hint at the balance of endurance and change in the face of passing time. This concept is contrasted with a warm and inviting golden floral print that can be seen to symbolize nature. Skillfully crafted, this bracelet is a stunning contemporary piece that is minimalist, creative and unique.</p>
<p>Bog Oak is an exceptionally rare form of timber that is comparable to some of the most expensive tropical hardwoods. It is notable for high strength and magnificent beauty. Other common names of bog-wood include abanos and morta. Essentially, bog oak is oak wood in the early stages of fossilization. This type of wood cannot be produced artificially, so it can only be obtained from natural sources like peat bogs and river beds. Having been submerged in acidic, oxygen-free conditions, this type of wood takes literally hundreds, but more often thousands of years to "mature". During this time iron and minerals from the water bind with tannin in the wood, resulting in a considerably darker, golden-brown to pure black color, as well as a significantly increased hardness and density. Due to this density, bog oak can only be carved with exceptionally firm tools.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/woodoo-bog-oak-and-leather-bracelet-with-golden-floral-print-w05">WooDoo Bog Oak Bracelet with Floral Print W05</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A conceptual piece, this bracelet is made with extremely rare and valuable bog oak. The look of the centerpiece on a minimalist leather strap mimics that of a watch, except the watch-face is replaced with a print. This golden floral print stands out elegantly, adding some welcome warmth to the all black color scheme. The aesthetics of bog oak, which takes thousands of years to mature, hint at the endurance, change and immensity of passing time. This concept is contrasted with a warm and inviting golden floral print that can be seen to symbolize nature. Skillfully crafted, this bracelet is a stunning contemporary piece that is minimalist, creative and unique.</p>
<h4>Materials</h4>
<p>Bog Oak is an exceptionally rare form of timber that is comparable to some of the most expensive tropical hardwoods. It is notable for high strength and magnificent beauty. Other common names of bog-wood include abanos and morta. Essentially, bog oak is oak wood in the early stages of fossilization. This type of wood cannot be produced artificially, so it can only be obtained from natural sources like peat bogs and river beds. Having been submerged in acidic, oxygen-free conditions, this type of wood takes literally hundreds, but more often thousands of years to &#8220;mature&#8221;. During this time iron and minerals from the water bind with tannin in the wood, resulting in a considerably darker, golden-brown to pure black color, as well as a significantly increased hardness and density. Due to this density, bog oak can only be carved with exceptionally firm tools.</p>
<p>Since supply of bog oak is so limited, prices for this type of wood are quite high. This is attributable to the fact that sites of bog oak are extremely rare and hard to access. The recovery of bog-wood trunks is often a difficult and engaging process, requiring meticulous preparation. At the same time, the much anticipated moment of extraction is the wood&#8217;s first exposure to light in hundreds and thousands of years. Extracted bog-wood is very delicate and requires complex desiccation. Nevertheless, despite great care most of the raw wood is not suitable for processing. Processing itself is notoriously unpredictable as some parts may be supple, while others very hard. All of this implies high value of raw and processed bog-oak wood.</p>
<p>From the viewpoint of aesthetics, bog-oak is a genuine experience of naturally formed color. This is particularly appealing to material connoisseurs who point to exquisite permeation of wood structure by the dark and noble color. The authenticity of this wood is complemented by its texture and grain. Parts of the wood may become combined, creating variations in color, as well as direction of growth rings. This imperfect appearance often adds to the aesthetic of bog-wood, conveying a powerful message of intensity of the past times, as well as longevity of the wood and the fact of its remaining intact. It may very well be the reason why in the nineteenth century bog oak was used to make exceptionally beautiful carved decorative jewelry.</p>
<p>As to the symbolism and metaphysical properties associated with the materials used in this bracelet, oak is one of the most sacred trees that stands for the invocation of wisdom, authority, endurance, strength and protection. Oak is also believed to bring vitality and long life and is considered among the most powerful and sacred Druid woods. In Ancient Celtic culture oak was considered to be the protector. Oak wood is also used as healing wood and is believed to aid in focusing the mind on the task at hand. Oak is said to inspire bravery, presence, leadership and enduring strength.</p>
<h4>About WooDoo</h4>
<p>WooDoo is an incredibly magnetic contemporary jewelry brand unlike any other. WooDoo is concerned with creative exploration of space, its geometric properties, as well as the possibilities of their tangible expression. All of this combines into a very original and unique aesthetic. WooDoo&#8217;s works are true artistic explorations of the properties of space. These explorations stem from visions of space that get translated into the physical world by means of minimalist tangible objects. But even after receiving physical form, WooDoo&#8217;s jewelry pieces feel deeply rooted in the realm of creative and visionary.</p>
<p>WooDoo&#8217;s accessories are truly memorable, commanding attention and recognition and are handcrafted from a number of select tactile precious woods, like African Blackwood or Purpleheart Wood. Each of WooDoo&#8217;s jewelry pieces carries an unmistakably modern, contemporary jewelry aesthetic. It is this aesthetic, along with skillful execution that WooDoo&#8217;s accessories owe to the duo of creative designers, standing behind this unique and visionary brand.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/woodoo-bog-oak-and-leather-bracelet-with-golden-floral-print-w05">WooDoo Bog Oak Bracelet with Floral Print W05</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/woodoo-bog-oak-and-leather-bracelet-with-golden-floral-print-w05/feed</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
