<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>chain ring bracelet &#8211; Nuage Showroom</title>
	<atom:link href="https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product-tag/chain-ring-bracelet/feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage</link>
	<description>Our Clothing &#38; Accessories</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2018 02:02:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Tsumi Chain-Ring Bracelet with Hematite TS140</title>
		<link>https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/tsumi-chain-ring-bracelet-with-hematite-ts140</link>
		<comments>https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/tsumi-chain-ring-bracelet-with-hematite-ts140#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2016 15:44:18 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onewithclouds]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/?post_type=product&#038;p=74</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Chain-ring bracelet is a unique accessory that is associated with a number of cultures around the world, but most notably with traditional Hindu jewelry. This particular chain-ring bracelet is a modern interpretation of this traditional, elegant and feminine design. An interpretation that is inspired by the notions of protection and armor. The total length of this medium-sized accessory is 18.5cm (7.28"). This bracelet consists of metal elements, a silver-plated chain, as well as a number of elongated hematite beads. It is these shiny beads that set the mood for this unique accessory. At the same time, the original design, monochrome color palette and an impeccable selection of materials allow this chain-ring bracelet to make a truly outstanding and lasting impression.</p>
<p>Materials: Hematite, Metal Elements, Silver Plated Chain, Sterling Silver Logo Charm. Medium length - 18.5 cm (7.28").</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/tsumi-chain-ring-bracelet-with-hematite-ts140">Tsumi Chain-Ring Bracelet with Hematite TS140</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Chain-ring bracelet is a unique accessory that is associated with a number of cultures around the world, but most notably with traditional Hindu jewelry. This particular chain-ring bracelet is a modern interpretation of this traditional, elegant and feminine design. An interpretation that is inspired by the notions of protection and armor. The total length of this medium-sized accessory is 18.5cm (7.28&#8243;). This bracelet consists of metal elements, a silver-plated chain, as well as a number of elongated hematite beads. It is these shiny beads that set the mood for this unique accessory. At the same time, the original design, monochrome color palette and an impeccable selection of materials allow this chain-ring bracelet to make a truly outstanding and lasting impression.</p>
<h4>Materials</h4>
<p>Hematite is one of the prettiest and most unique crystals used in jewelry accessories. This crystal provides a unique combination of shiny charisma, while retaining the ability to remain reserved. It is one of the few magnetic crystals the structure of which is dominated by iron. Hematite is often referred to as a ‘seeker crystal’ that helps one find a new path or approach to gain something you desire, but not yet posses. Hematite crystals are thought to have great grounding and balancing effect, as well as serving to stimulate mind, memory, sometimes evoking deep thought.</p>
<h4>About Tsumi</h4>
<p>Tsumi is a brand born from the love of fashion, as well as an inherent need to be original and unique. Each Tsumi accessory is infused by a touch of authentic ethnic flair and is inspired by joyful memories of traveling the world. Tsumi accessories are crafted with an incredible skill, while remaining visionary and creative pieces of contemporary jewelry.</p>
<p>Most of Tsumi accessories are made in either limited quantity or in one unique specimen. Tsumi is also synonymous with an exceptional selection of original and rare materials used to create their stylish accessories. These include semi-precious stones, corals, pearls and crystals, making Tsumi jewelry not only an embodiment of original style, but also an experience.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/tsumi-chain-ring-bracelet-with-hematite-ts140">Tsumi Chain-Ring Bracelet with Hematite TS140</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/tsumi-chain-ring-bracelet-with-hematite-ts140/feed</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
