<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>wearable sculpture &#8211; Nuage Showroom</title>
	<atom:link href="https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product-tag/wearable-sculpture/feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage</link>
	<description>Our Clothing &#38; Accessories</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2018 02:02:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Francoise Oz Faience Ring with Black Glazing FR01</title>
		<link>https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/francoise-oz-faience-ring-black-glossy-glazing-fr01</link>
		<comments>https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/francoise-oz-faience-ring-black-glossy-glazing-fr01#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2016 19:41:17 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onewithclouds]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/?post_type=product&#038;p=351</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>This beautiful one-of-a-kind ring is the definition of an original accessory. It has a sense of true presence, which it conveys through its beautifully organic design. One might infer that the design is fantasy-inspired, yet the ring is very real. This particular example of Francoise Oz creativity and craftsmanship is a larger type of ring. The latter might be the reason why it is giving off a spectacular wearable sculpture vibe.</p>
<p>Francoise Oz rings are exclusives that come in only one ring size, listed below. We highly recommend you to consider <a href="http://www.ringsizes.co/info.html" target="_blank">the factors outlined here</a> when determining your ring size, as well as consulting this <a href="http://www.ringsizes.co/" target="_blank">excellent ring size conversion chart</a>. If you need help determining your ring size, contact us through the chat app on this site.</p>
<p>[table id=9 /]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/francoise-oz-faience-ring-black-glossy-glazing-fr01">Francoise Oz Faience Ring with Black Glazing FR01</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This beautiful one-of-a-kind ring is the definition of an original accessory. It has a sense of true presence, which it conveys through its beautiful organic design. One might infer that the design is fantasy-inspired, yet the ring feels very real. This particular example of Francoise Oz creativity and craftsmanship is a larger type of ring. The latter might be the reason why it is giving off a spectacular wearable sculpture vibe.</p>
<h4>About Francoise Oz</h4>
<p>Francoise Oz is an exquisite contemporary wearable sculpture brand with a distinct, unconventional, contemporary aesthetic. The process of creation of jewelry from faience and clay, employed by Francoise Oz is meticulous and labor-intensive. Francoise Oz&#8217;s wonderful creations are taking shape through forming raw material, firing, then grinding the fired earthenware pieces by hand and glazing. The resulting pieces are stylish, artistic and absolutely unique. No wonder, Francoise Oz&#8217;s faience and ceramic accessories are endorsed by fashion and design connoisseurs worldwide.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/francoise-oz-faience-ring-black-glossy-glazing-fr01">Francoise Oz Faience Ring with Black Glazing FR01</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/francoise-oz-faience-ring-black-glossy-glazing-fr01/feed</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Francoise Oz Faience Ring with Black Glazing FR02</title>
		<link>https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/francoise-oz-faience-ring-with-black-glazing-fr02</link>
		<comments>https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/francoise-oz-faience-ring-with-black-glazing-fr02#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2016 20:55:06 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onewithclouds]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/?post_type=product&#038;p=381</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>This beautiful one-of-a-kind ring is the definition of an original accessory. It has a sense of true presence, which it conveys through its beautifully organic design. One might infer that the design is fantasy-inspired, yet the ring is very real. This particular example of creativity and craftsmanship is different from its Francoise Oz counterparts, as it is smaller than the rest of its siblings. Thus, making the ring a bit more reserved and more universal. It is this very quality that will allow you to pair this stunning wearable sculpture accessory with more of your favorite looks.</p>
<p>Francoise Oz rings are exclusives that come in only one ring size, listed below. We highly recommend you to consider <a href="http://www.ringsizes.co/info.html" target="_blank">the factors outlined here</a> when determining your ring size, as well as consulting this <a href="http://www.ringsizes.co/" target="_blank">excellent ring size conversion chart</a>. If you need help determining your ring size, contact us through the chat app on this site.</p>
<p>[table id=8 /]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/francoise-oz-faience-ring-with-black-glazing-fr02">Francoise Oz Faience Ring with Black Glazing FR02</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This beautiful one-of-a-kind ring is the definition of an original accessory. It has a sense of true presence, which it conveys through its beautiful organic design. One might infer that the design is fantasy-inspired, yet the ring feels very real. This particular example of creativity and craftsmanship is different from its Francoise Oz counterparts, as it is smaller than the rest of its siblings. This makes the ring a bit more reserved and universal. It is this very quality that will allow you to pair this stunning wearable sculpture accessory with more of your favorite looks.</p>
<h4>About Francoise Oz</h4>
<p>Francoise Oz is an exquisite contemporary wearable sculpture brand with an unconventional, contemporary aesthetic. The process of creation of jewelry from faience and clay, employed by Francoise Oz is meticulous and labor-intensive. Francoise Oz&#8217;s wonderful creations are taking shape through forming raw material, firing, then grinding the fired earthenware pieces by hand and glazing. The resulting pieces are stylish, artistic and absolutely unique. No wonder, Francoise Oz&#8217;s faience and ceramic accessories are endorsed by fashion and design connoisseurs worldwide.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/francoise-oz-faience-ring-with-black-glazing-fr02">Francoise Oz Faience Ring with Black Glazing FR02</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/francoise-oz-faience-ring-with-black-glazing-fr02/feed</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Francoise Oz Matte Ceramic Ring with Metallic Flaking FR03</title>
		<link>https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/francoise-oz-ceramic-ring-with-metallic-flaking-fr03</link>
		<comments>https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/francoise-oz-ceramic-ring-with-metallic-flaking-fr03#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2016 23:44:02 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onewithclouds]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/?post_type=product&#038;p=402</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>This beautiful one-of-a-kind ring is the definition of an original accessory. It has a sense of true presence, which it conveys through its beautifully organic design. One might infer that the design is fantasy-inspired, yet the ring is very real. This particular example of Francoise Oz creativity and craftsmanship is a larger type of ring. It is also special in a way that it's incredible non-glazed ceramics include a myriad of metallic flakes. Also, from a certain angle you can clearly see it as resembling a teddy bear. Overall, this stunning accessory is giving off a spectacular wearable sculpture vibe.</p>
<p>Francoise Oz rings are exclusives that come in only one ring size, listed below. We highly recommend you to consider <a href="http://www.ringsizes.co/info.html" target="_blank">the factors outlined here</a> when determining your ring size, as well as consulting this <a href="http://www.ringsizes.co/" target="_blank">excellent ring size conversion chart</a>. If you need help determining your ring size, contact us through the chat app on this site.</p>
<p>[table id=7 /]</p>
<p>&#160;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/francoise-oz-ceramic-ring-with-metallic-flaking-fr03">Francoise Oz Matte Ceramic Ring with Metallic Flaking FR03</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This beautiful one-of-a-kind ring is the definition of an original accessory. It has a sense of true presence, which it conveys through its beautiful organic design. One might infer that the design is fantasy-inspired, yet the ring feels very real. This particular example of Francoise Oz creativity and craftsmanship is a larger type of ring. It is also special in a way that it&#8217;s incredible non-glazed ceramics include a myriad of metallic flakes. Also, from a certain angle you can clearly see it as resembling a teddy bear. Overall, this stunning accessory is giving off a spectacular wearable sculpture vibe.</p>
<h4>About Francoise Oz</h4>
<p>Francoise Oz is an exquisite contemporary wearable sculpture brand with an unconventional, contemporary aesthetic. The process of creation of jewelry from faience and clay, employed by Francoise Oz is meticulous and labor-intensive. Francoise Oz&#8217;s wonderful creations are taking shape through forming raw material, firing, then grinding the fired earthenware pieces by hand and glazing. The resulting pieces are stylish, artistic and absolutely unique. No wonder, Francoise Oz&#8217;s faience and ceramic accessories are endorsed by fashion and design connoisseurs worldwide.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/francoise-oz-ceramic-ring-with-metallic-flaking-fr03">Francoise Oz Matte Ceramic Ring with Metallic Flaking FR03</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/francoise-oz-ceramic-ring-with-metallic-flaking-fr03/feed</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
