<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>artificial stone &#8211; Nuage Showroom</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/wpstatic/product-tag/artificial-stone/feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://localhost/wpstatic</link>
	<description>Our Clothing &#38; Accessories</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 01:55:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>WooDoo Engineered Stone Earrings W17</title>
		<link>http://localhost/wpstatic/product/woodoo-artificial-stone-earrings-polished-w17</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2016 16:19:59 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onewithclouds]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/wpstatic/?post_type=product&#038;p=296</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>These wonderful earrings were recreated by WooDoo on our special request in extremely rare and valuable African Blackwood. This request was made specifically to complement WooDoo's casual <a href="http://localhost/wpstatic/product/woodoo-deer-antler-ring-polished-w10" target="_blank">Deer Antler W10</a> ring. The earrings are complete with delicate and graceful silver pins. Fluent, unique and minimalist, these earrings have a sense of presence and style that is easily recognizable and truly memorable.</p>
<p>Engineered Stone is a material that considerably improves upon the properties of natural stone. Engineered stone was invented in Italy in early 1980s by Marcello Toncelli, founder of world-renowned Breton S.P.A. This type of stone is tailor-made with a mix of stone/marble powder, low-viscosity/high-strength epoxy or resin, a supplement of coloring, stabilizers and UV absorbing additives. To complement stone/marble powder aggregates, materials like colored glass or metal flakes can be added. Depending on the composition of stone powders and their intended application, there exist two major types of engineered stone - marble and quartz.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic/product/woodoo-artificial-stone-earrings-polished-w17">WooDoo Engineered Stone Earrings W17</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>These wonderful earrings were created by WooDoo to complement the casual <a href="http://localhost/wpstatic/product/woodoo-deer-antler-ring-polished-w10" target="_blank">Deer Antler W10</a> ring. The earrings are complete with delicate and graceful silver pins. Fluent, unique and minimalist, these earrings have a sense of presence and style that is easily recognizable and truly memorable.</p>
<h4>Materials</h4>
<p>Engineered Stone is a material that considerably improves upon the properties of natural stone. Engineered stone was invented in Italy in early 1980s by Marcello Toncelli, founder of world-renowned Breton S.P.A. This type of stone is tailor-made with a mix of stone/marble powder, low-viscosity/high-strength epoxy or resin, a supplement of coloring, stabilizers and UV absorbing additives. To complement stone/marble powder aggregates, materials like colored glass or metal flakes can be added. Depending on the composition of stone powders and their intended application, there exist two major types of engineered stone &#8211; marble and quartz.</p>
<p>Engineered stone is mainly worked with a water jet cutter or a diamond blade. It is less porous, exhibiting a uniform structure without any hidden internal cracks or flaws. The binding resin allows for some flexibility, preventing engineered stone from cracking. This property decreases over time, as resins continue to harden during a product&#8217;s lifetime. It is worth noting that engineered stone is not completely UV stable, so a very long exposure to UV light might result in color changes and breakdown of the epoxy or resin binding agents.</p>
<h4>About WooDoo</h4>
<p>WooDoo is an extraordinary, magnetic, and minimalist jewelry brand. WooDoo is about creative exploration of space and its geometric properties. WooDoo&#8217;s quest is an inquiry into the possibilities of tangible expression of this visionary aesthetic. This brand&#8217;s jewelry transcends the realm of physical, bridging the tangible and the creative.</p>
<p>WooDoo pieces are majestic and truly memorable, while being handcrafted from a number of select precious woods, including African Blackwood, Bog Oak or Purpleheart Wood. Each of the brand&#8217;s pieces is an original and unique experience of jewelry aesthetic. It is this aesthetic, along with skillful execution that WooDoo&#8217;s accessories owe to the duo of creative designers standing behind this visionary brand.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic/product/woodoo-artificial-stone-earrings-polished-w17">WooDoo Engineered Stone Earrings W17</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
