<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>rose quartz &#8211; Nuage Showroom</title>
	<atom:link href="https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product-tag/rose-quartz/feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage</link>
	<description>Our Clothing &#38; Accessories</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2018 02:02:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Miracle Rose Quartz Crystal Bracelet M09</title>
		<link>https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/miracle-rose-quartz-bracelet-m09</link>
		<comments>https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/miracle-rose-quartz-bracelet-m09#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 10:58:02 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onewithclouds]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/?post_type=product&#038;p=347</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>This bracelet is a unique accessory exemplifying Miracle's trademark fusion of historic jewelry tradition with stylistic cues and elegance of modern contemporary jewelry aesthetic. The bracelet is 16.5cm (6.5") long and is based on a larger chain complemented by creatively combined beads that provide tasteful accents to the overall color scheme. The centerpiece of the bracelet is an element of Rose Quartz, a crystal that has always been considered a symbol of unconditional love. This beautiful accessory shares refinement and style that will perfectly complement Miracle's incredible necklaces.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/miracle-rose-quartz-bracelet-m09">Miracle Rose Quartz Crystal Bracelet M09</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This bracelet is a unique accessory exemplifying Miracle&#8217;s trademark fusion of historic jewelry tradition with stylistic cues and elegance of modern contemporary jewelry aesthetic. The bracelet is 16.5cm (6.5&#8243;) long and is based on a larger chain complemented by creatively combined beads that provide tasteful accents to the overall color scheme. The centerpiece of the bracelet is an element of Rose Quartz, a crystal that has always been considered a symbol of unconditional love. This beautiful accessory shares refinement and style that will perfectly complement Miracle&#8217;s incredible necklaces.</p>
<h4>Materials</h4>
<p>Love is one of the most fundamental and powerful forces in the world. At the same time the color of a pink rose is considered an unmistakable symbol of tenderness, romance and love. Could it be the reason why, in the world of semi-precious gemstones natural Rose Quartz is a crystal  of heartfelt unconditional love, femininity, compassion, healing and romance. It is believed that Rose Quartz can unravel the heart&#8217;s deep inner love not only for others, but also for oneself, allowing to rekindle the appreciation of beauty, nature and art. In this way, Rose Quartz can provide a sense of personal fulfillment and contentment, helping to regain the capacity to truly give and receive love from others.  This crystal is also believed to be effective in developing relationships with family and friends, as well as attracting romance and new love.</p>
<h4>About Miracle</h4>
<p>Miracle is a unique brand that is based in refined, sophisticated and feminine accessories. Accessories that combine a sense of jewelry tradition with notions of elegant, modern and contemporary jewelry. Truly a designer brand, Miracle seems to embody the commitment to a woman&#8217;s passion for outstanding accessories, creating undeniably beautiful pieces, from necklaces to earrings and bracelets. Miracle&#8217;s apt selection of favorite materials includes howlite, quartz, cat&#8217;s eye and agate. Taking a piece of Miracle&#8217;s jewelry into a hand, one can&#8217;t help but acknowledge the brand&#8217;s unmistakable original style that combines true refinement with sensual elegance.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/miracle-rose-quartz-bracelet-m09">Miracle Rose Quartz Crystal Bracelet M09</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/miracle-rose-quartz-bracelet-m09/feed</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
