<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>unique design &#8211; Nuage Showroom</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/wpstatic/product-tag/unique-design/feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://localhost/wpstatic</link>
	<description>Our Clothing &#38; Accessories</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 01:55:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Tsumi Blue Coral and Howlite Neclace TS182</title>
		<link>http://localhost/wpstatic/product/tsumi-necklace-blue-coral-howlite-ts182</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2016 15:10:27 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onewithclouds]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/wpstatic/?post_type=product&#038;p=60</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>This absolutely fantastic necklace made of howlite, glass, hematite and blue coral is inspired by tribal customs and traditions, as well as ritual dances. An adjustable necklace clasp allows to vary the length of this item within 52cm (20.47"). This luxurious necklace is made with a number of small triangular coral beads, with authentic traces of cutting and an absolutely unique natural blue hue.  Smooth facets of the coral beads are pleasant to the touch, while their arrangement provides the necklace with a sense of genuine volume that is rare of this type of jewelry. This kind of blue coral is mined only on the shoals of the Gulf of Biafra, located on African West Coast near Cameroon. Overall, blue triangular corals are complemented with elliptical howlite beads giving this necklace a feeling of unique and authentic charm, as well as a true sense of presence.</p>
<p>Materials: Howlite, Blue Corals, Glass, Metal Elements, Sterling Silver Logo Charm. Length adjustable up to 52 cm (20.47").</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic/product/tsumi-necklace-blue-coral-howlite-ts182">Tsumi Blue Coral and Howlite Neclace TS182</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This absolutely fantastic necklace made of howlite, glass, hematite and blue coral is inspired by tribal customs and traditions, as well as ritual dances. An adjustable necklace clasp allows to vary the length of this item within 52cm (20.47&#8243;). This luxurious necklace is made with a number of small triangular coral beads, with authentic traces of cutting and an absolutely unique natural blue hue.  Smooth facets of the coral beads are pleasant to the touch, while their arrangement provides the necklace with a sense of genuine volume that is rare of this type of jewelry. This kind of blue coral is mined only on the shoals of the Gulf of Biafra, located on African West Coast near Cameroon. Overall, blue triangular corals are complemented with elliptical howlite beads giving this necklace a feeling of unique and authentic charm, as well as a true sense of presence.</p>
<h4>Materials</h4>
<p>Since the ancient times coral is a traditional gift of protection for the expectant mother or a newborn child. Coral is also associated with emotional healing. Blue coral in particular is believed to have an ability of reconnecting oneself to one&#8217;s inner child, providing stability, reducing fear and finding inner peace. Coral is also believed to extend its protection to anyone living, traveling or working by/in the sea. Since coral is of organic origin, it is often thought of as an aid in rekindling one&#8217;s relationship with nature and its wonders, stimulating creativity and optimism, as well as enabling it&#8217;s bearer to enjoy life to the fullest. It may be the reason why, all around the world, coral has been used as jewelry for at least thousands of years.</p>
<p>Howlite is considered to be a stone of calm and tranquility. A stone that can calm and soothe the emotions, help cope with an overactive mind and achieve a deep and restful sleep. Howlite is believed to reduce conflicts, facilitate communication, promote kindness, compassion and peaceful coexistence.  This truly beautiful and tranquil gem is believed to aid in clarifying one’s mind to develop a more prominent awareness of one’s ambitions and goals. Often referred to as an ‘attunement stone’, Howlite is thought to help expand the horizons and open the mind to wisdom and new knowledge.</p>
<h4>About Tsumi</h4>
<p>Tsumi is a brand born from the love of fashion, as well as an inherent need to be original and unique. Each Tsumi accessory is infused by a touch of authentic ethnic flair and is inspired by joyful memories of traveling the world. Tsumi accessories are crafted with an incredible skill, while remaining visionary and creative pieces of contemporary jewelry.</p>
<p>Most of Tsumi accessories are made in either limited quantity or in one unique specimen. Tsumi is also synonymous with an exceptional selection of original and rare materials used to create their stylish accessories. These include semi-precious stones, corals, pearls and crystals, making Tsumi jewelry not only an embodiment of original style, but also an experience.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic/product/tsumi-necklace-blue-coral-howlite-ts182">Tsumi Blue Coral and Howlite Neclace TS182</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tsumi Chain-Ring Bracelet with Hematite TS140</title>
		<link>http://localhost/wpstatic/product/tsumi-chain-ring-bracelet-with-hematite-ts140</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2016 15:44:18 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onewithclouds]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/wpstatic/?post_type=product&#038;p=74</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Chain-ring bracelet is a unique accessory that is associated with a number of cultures around the world, but most notably with traditional Hindu jewelry. This particular chain-ring bracelet is a modern interpretation of this traditional, elegant and feminine design. An interpretation that is inspired by the notions of protection and armor. The total length of this medium-sized accessory is 18.5cm (7.28"). This bracelet consists of metal elements, a silver-plated chain, as well as a number of elongated hematite beads. It is these shiny beads that set the mood for this unique accessory. At the same time, the original design, monochrome color palette and an impeccable selection of materials allow this chain-ring bracelet to make a truly outstanding and lasting impression.</p>
<p>Materials: Hematite, Metal Elements, Silver Plated Chain, Sterling Silver Logo Charm. Medium length - 18.5 cm (7.28").</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic/product/tsumi-chain-ring-bracelet-with-hematite-ts140">Tsumi Chain-Ring Bracelet with Hematite TS140</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Chain-ring bracelet is a unique accessory that is associated with a number of cultures around the world, but most notably with traditional Hindu jewelry. This particular chain-ring bracelet is a modern interpretation of this traditional, elegant and feminine design. An interpretation that is inspired by the notions of protection and armor. The total length of this medium-sized accessory is 18.5cm (7.28&#8243;). This bracelet consists of metal elements, a silver-plated chain, as well as a number of elongated hematite beads. It is these shiny beads that set the mood for this unique accessory. At the same time, the original design, monochrome color palette and an impeccable selection of materials allow this chain-ring bracelet to make a truly outstanding and lasting impression.</p>
<h4>Materials</h4>
<p>Hematite is one of the prettiest and most unique crystals used in jewelry accessories. This crystal provides a unique combination of shiny charisma, while retaining the ability to remain reserved. It is one of the few magnetic crystals the structure of which is dominated by iron. Hematite is often referred to as a ‘seeker crystal’ that helps one find a new path or approach to gain something you desire, but not yet posses. Hematite crystals are thought to have great grounding and balancing effect, as well as serving to stimulate mind, memory, sometimes evoking deep thought.</p>
<h4>About Tsumi</h4>
<p>Tsumi is a brand born from the love of fashion, as well as an inherent need to be original and unique. Each Tsumi accessory is infused by a touch of authentic ethnic flair and is inspired by joyful memories of traveling the world. Tsumi accessories are crafted with an incredible skill, while remaining visionary and creative pieces of contemporary jewelry.</p>
<p>Most of Tsumi accessories are made in either limited quantity or in one unique specimen. Tsumi is also synonymous with an exceptional selection of original and rare materials used to create their stylish accessories. These include semi-precious stones, corals, pearls and crystals, making Tsumi jewelry not only an embodiment of original style, but also an experience.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic/product/tsumi-chain-ring-bracelet-with-hematite-ts140">Tsumi Chain-Ring Bracelet with Hematite TS140</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tsumi Hematite, Volcanic Lava Rock and Pyrite Necklace TS203</title>
		<link>http://localhost/wpstatic/product/tsumi-necklace-hematite-pyrite-volcanic-lava-ts203</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2016 14:42:19 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onewithclouds]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/wpstatic/?post_type=product&#038;p=48</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Minimalist and elegant, this gorgeous necklace is a testament to the beauty and timelessness of authentic and original design. Inspired by the Moon, this necklace is not only photogenic, but also absolutely stunning when experienced in person. In the hand, this necklace feels pleasant to the touch with its materials harmoniously complementing each other and its minimal design emanating an atmosphere of completeness. The materials used in this item include symmetrically arranged elements of hematite, as well as a rich golden brown pyrite mineral that adorns a brass chain extension. Adding to the unique atmospheric charm of this composition are two cubic volcanic lava beads. Overall, this is a minimalist masterpiece showcasing the creative vision, experience and skill of Iwona Domanska, an incredible designer behind the Tsumi brand.</p>
<p>Materials: Hematite, Brass, Lava Rock (Volcanic Rock), Pyrite. Front Drop - 21 cm (8.27").</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic/product/tsumi-necklace-hematite-pyrite-volcanic-lava-ts203">Tsumi Hematite, Volcanic Lava Rock and Pyrite Necklace TS203</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Minimalist and elegant, this gorgeous necklace is a testament to the beauty and timelessness of authentic and original design. Inspired by the Moon, this necklace is not only photogenic, but also absolutely stunning when experienced in person. In the hand, this necklace feels pleasant to the touch with its materials harmoniously complementing each other and its minimal design emanating an atmosphere of completeness. The materials used in this item include symmetrically arranged elements of hematite, as well as a rich golden brown pyrite mineral that adorns a brass chain extension. Adding to the unique atmospheric charm of this composition are two cubic volcanic lava beads. Overall, this is a minimalist masterpiece showcasing the creative vision, experience and skill of Iwona Domanska, an incredible designer behind the Tsumi brand.</p>
<h4>Materials</h4>
<p>Pyrite is a stunning mineral that bears incredible resemblance to gold. The fire is often sad to be hidden with its gleaming beauty. Pyrite is a stone that is brought to life by striking it against another stone or metal, producing plentiful sparks. Hence this mineral is often appearing as a stone of action vitality and will. A stone that taps into a person&#8217;s abilities and potential. This beautiful stone is believed to bring confidence and persistence to carry things to completion. A stone with a strong connection to Earth element, it closely resonates with Fire as well, providing for a symbolic connection between the two. Pyrite is often thought of as reminiscent of the warmth and lasting presence of the sun, as well as the ability to generate desirable outcomes by one&#8217;s own power.</p>
<p>Hematite is one of the prettiest and most unique crystals used in jewelry accessories. This crystal provides a unique combination of shiny charisma, while retaining the ability to remain reserved. It is one of the few magnetic crystals the structure of which is dominated by iron. Hematite is often referred to as a &#8216;seeker crystal&#8217; that helps one find a new path or approach to gain something you desire, but not yet posses. Hematite crystals are thought to have great grounding and balancing effect, as well as serving to stimulate mind, memory, sometimes evoking deep thought.</p>
<p>Lava rock, volcanic rock or basalt is a beautiful matte black stone with an incredible texture. It is believed to be an excellent grounding stone, strengthening one&#8217;s connection to Mother Earth and providing stability in the time of change. Lava rock is also often thought of as a physical embodiment of fire, being a stone that started as fiery molten lava, subsequently turning into rock.</p>
<h4>About Tsumi</h4>
<p>Tsumi is a brand born from the love of fashion, as well as an inherent need to be original and unique. Each Tsumi accessory is infused by a touch of authentic ethnic flair and is inspired by joyful memories of traveling the world. Tsumi accessories are crafted with an incredible skill, while remaining visionary and creative pieces of contemporary jewelry.</p>
<p>Most of Tsumi accessories are made in either limited quantity or in one unique specimen. Tsumi is also synonymous with an exceptional selection of original and rare materials used to create their stylish accessories. These include semi-precious stones, corals, pearls and crystals, making Tsumi jewelry not only an embodiment of original style, but also an experience.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic/product/tsumi-necklace-hematite-pyrite-volcanic-lava-ts203">Tsumi Hematite, Volcanic Lava Rock and Pyrite Necklace TS203</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tsumi Howlite and Hematite Necklace TS188</title>
		<link>http://localhost/wpstatic/product/tsumi-howlite-hematite-necklace-ts188</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2016 15:04:28 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onewithclouds]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/wpstatic/?post_type=product&#038;p=55</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>This charming necklace is created in orange/black color scheme with blue accents and is bound to complement some of your finest looks. Quite a bit atmospheric and airy, this beautiful piece carries a playful feeling of lightness and easiness that is well accentuated by several rows of chains, framing the bottom of the necklace. The length of the necklace can be conveniently adjusted up to 65 cm (25.59"). The creation of this beautiful accessory is inspired by tribal customs and traditions, as well as ritual dances. Aptly, the choice of materials includes howlite, hematite and bone, as well metal elements and a sterling silver logo charm. Markedly, howlite is one of the earliest minded minerals to be used in jewelry-making, highly appreciated in the ancient Middle East.</p>
<p>Materials: Hematite, Howlite, Bone, Metal Chains, Sterling Silver Logo Charm. Length adjustable up to 65 cm (25.59").</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic/product/tsumi-howlite-hematite-necklace-ts188">Tsumi Howlite and Hematite Necklace TS188</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This charming necklace is created in orange/black color scheme with blue accents and is bound to complement some of your finest looks. Quite a bit atmospheric and airy, this beautiful piece carries a playful feeling of lightness and easiness that is well accentuated by several rows of chains, framing the bottom of the necklace. The length of the necklace can be conveniently adjusted up to 65 cm (25.59&#8243;). The creation of this beautiful accessory is inspired by tribal customs and traditions, as well as ritual dances. Aptly, the choice of materials includes howlite, hematite and bone, as well metal elements and a sterling silver logo charm. Markedly, howlite is one of the earliest minded minerals to be used in jewelry-making, highly appreciated in the ancient Middle East.</p>
<h4>Materials</h4>
<p>Hematite is one of the prettiest and most unique crystals used in jewelry accessories. This crystal provides a unique combination of shiny charisma, while retaining the ability to remain reserved. It is one of the few magnetic crystals the structure of which is dominated by iron. Hematite is often referred to as a &#8216;seeker crystal&#8217; that helps one find a new path or approach to gain something you desire, but not yet posses. Hematite crystals are thought to have great grounding and balancing effect, as well as serving to stimulate mind, memory, sometimes evoking deep thought.</p>
<p>Since the ancient times, Howlite is considered to be a stone of calm and tranquility. A stone that can calm and soothe the emotions, help cope with an overactive mind and achieve a deep and restful sleep. Howlite is believed to reduce conflicts, facilitate communication, promote kindness, compassion and peaceful coexistence.  This truly beautiful and tranquil gem is believed to aid in clarifying one&#8217;s mind to develop a more prominent awareness of one&#8217;s ambitions and goals. Often referred to as an &#8216;attunement stone&#8217;, Howlite is thought to help expand the horizons and open the mind to wisdom and new knowledge.</p>
<h4>About Tsumi</h4>
<p>Tsumi is a brand born from the love of fashion, as well as an inherent need to be original and unique. Each Tsumi accessory is infused by a touch of authentic ethnic flair and is inspired by joyful memories of traveling the world. Tsumi accessories are crafted with an incredible skill, while remaining visionary and creative pieces of contemporary jewelry.</p>
<p>Most of Tsumi accessories are made in either limited quantity or in one unique specimen. Tsumi is also synonymous with an exceptional selection of original and rare materials used to create their stylish accessories. These include semi-precious stones, corals, pearls and crystals, making Tsumi jewelry not only an embodiment of original style, but also an experience.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic/product/tsumi-howlite-hematite-necklace-ts188">Tsumi Howlite and Hematite Necklace TS188</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tsumi One-Of-A-Kind Azure Agate Necklace TS181</title>
		<link>http://localhost/wpstatic/product/tsumi-unique-necklace-lazur-agate-ts181</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2016 14:01:37 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onewithclouds]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/wpstatic/?post_type=product&#038;p=41</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>This one-of-a-kind accessory is inspired by tribal customs and ritual dancing. Minimalist and beautiful, this atmospheric necklace is adorned with a large azure agate. The structure of this unique stone is reminiscent of ocean waves as seen from a bird's eye view. Adjustable chain allows to vary the length of the necklace up to 55cm (21.65"). Howlite, metal and a sterling silver charm complement azure agate in this original and stylish composition.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic/product/tsumi-unique-necklace-lazur-agate-ts181">Tsumi One-Of-A-Kind Azure Agate Necklace TS181</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This one-of-a-kind accessory is inspired by tribal customs and ritual dancing. Minimalist and beautiful, this atmospheric necklace is adorned with a large azure agate. The structure of this unique stone is reminiscent of ocean waves as seen from a bird&#8217;s eye view. Adjustable chain allows to vary the length of the necklace up to 55cm (21.65&#8243;). Howlite, metal and a sterling silver charm complement azure agate in this original and stylish composition.</p>
<h4>Materials</h4>
<p>Agate is a magnificent  stone that is believed to have been one of humanity&#8217;s earliest possessions. According to researchers, Agate was mined in Ancient Egypt as early as 3500 B.C. As per Agate&#8217;s properties, it is regarded as providing a harmonizing influence. It is believed to help with balancing of emotional, physical and intellectual endeavors, harmonizing the Ying and Yang forces of the universe. A soothing and calming stone, Agate is thought to bring great strength gradually. This stone is said to aid with the acceptances of oneself, building self confidence. It is also believed that Agate can improve concentration and analytical abilities, resulting in newfound practical solutions.</p>
<h4>About Tsumi</h4>
<p>Tsumi is a brand born from the love of fashion, as well as an inherent need to be original and unique. Each Tsumi accessory is infused by a touch of authentic ethnic flair and is inspired by joyful memories of traveling the world. Tsumi accessories are crafted with an incredible skill, while remaining visionary and creative pieces of contemporary jewelry.</p>
<p>Most of Tsumi accessories are made in either limited quantity or in one unique specimen. Tsumi is also synonymous with an exceptional selection of original and rare materials used to create their stylish accessories. These include semi-precious stones, corals, pearls and crystals, making Tsumi jewelry not only an embodiment of original style, but also an experience.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic/product/tsumi-unique-necklace-lazur-agate-ts181">Tsumi One-Of-A-Kind Azure Agate Necklace TS181</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tsumi Volcanic Rock Necklace TS202</title>
		<link>http://localhost/wpstatic/product/tsumi-necklace-volcanic-lava-ts202</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2016 14:08:39 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onewithclouds]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/wpstatic/product/tsumi-necklace-volcanic-lava-ts202</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>An absolutely gorgeous accessory from the brand's latest collection, this volcanic lava necklace possesses the sophistication and a sense of style to make a truly memorable impression. Created in a silver/black color scheme, this necklace is remarkable for its beautiful detailing and gorgeous design. Skillfully crafted using a number of techniques, this necklace is inspired by the Moon. The highlight of the necklace are the volcanic lava and glass beads, a gracious silver-plated brass collar band, as well as a chain and satin tape. The front drop of this beautiful necklace measures 9cm (3.54").</p>
<p>Materials: Volcanic Rock (Lava Rock), Metal Chains, Glass, Satin Tape, Silver Plated Collar. Front Drop - 9 cm.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic/product/tsumi-necklace-volcanic-lava-ts202">Tsumi Volcanic Rock Necklace TS202</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An absolutely gorgeous accessory from the brand&#8217;s latest collection, this volcanic lava necklace possesses the sophistication and a sense of style to make a truly memorable impression. Created in a silver/black color scheme, this necklace is remarkable for its beautiful detailing and gorgeous design. Skillfully crafted using a number of techniques, this necklace is inspired by the Moon. The highlight of the necklace are the volcanic lava and glass beads, a gracious silver-plated brass collar band, as well as a chain and satin tape. The front drop of this beautiful necklace measures 9cm (3.54&#8243;).</p>
<h4>Materials</h4>
<p>Lava rock, volcanic rock or basalt is a beautiful matte black stone with an incredible texture. It is believed to be an excellent grounding stone, strengthening one&#8217;s connection to Mother Earth and providing stability in the time of change. Lava rock is also often thought of as a physical embodiment of fire, being a stone that started as fiery molten lava, subsequently turning into rock.</p>
<h4>About Tsumi</h4>
<p>Tsumi is a brand born from the love of fashion, as well as an inherent need to be original and unique. Each Tsumi accessory is infused by a touch of authentic ethnic flair and is inspired by joyful memories of traveling the world. Tsumi accessories are crafted with an incredible skill, while remaining visionary and creative pieces of contemporary jewelry.</p>
<p>Most of Tsumi accessories are made in either limited quantity or in one unique specimen. Tsumi is also synonymous with an exceptional selection of original and rare materials used to create their stylish accessories. These include semi-precious stones, corals, pearls and crystals, making Tsumi jewelry not only an embodiment of original style, but also an experience.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic/product/tsumi-necklace-volcanic-lava-ts202">Tsumi Volcanic Rock Necklace TS202</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://localhost/wpstatic">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
