<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>silver &#8211; Nuage Showroom</title>
	<atom:link href="http://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product-tag/silver/feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage</link>
	<description>Our Clothing &#38; Accessories</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 01:55:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Tsumi One-Of-A-Kind Azure Agate Necklace TS181</title>
		<link>http://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/tsumi-unique-necklace-lazur-agate-ts181</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2016 14:01:37 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onewithclouds]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/?post_type=product&#038;p=41</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>This one-of-a-kind accessory is inspired by tribal customs and ritual dancing. Minimalist and beautiful, this atmospheric necklace is adorned with a large azure agate. The structure of this unique stone is reminiscent of ocean waves as seen from a bird's eye view. Adjustable chain allows to vary the length of the necklace up to 55cm (21.65"). Howlite, metal and a sterling silver charm complement azure agate in this original and stylish composition.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/tsumi-unique-necklace-lazur-agate-ts181">Tsumi One-Of-A-Kind Azure Agate Necklace TS181</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This one-of-a-kind accessory is inspired by tribal customs and ritual dancing. Minimalist and beautiful, this atmospheric necklace is adorned with a large azure agate. The structure of this unique stone is reminiscent of ocean waves as seen from a bird&#8217;s eye view. Adjustable chain allows to vary the length of the necklace up to 55cm (21.65&#8243;). Howlite, metal and a sterling silver charm complement azure agate in this original and stylish composition.</p>
<h4>Materials</h4>
<p>Agate is a magnificent  stone that is believed to have been one of humanity&#8217;s earliest possessions. According to researchers, Agate was mined in Ancient Egypt as early as 3500 B.C. As per Agate&#8217;s properties, it is regarded as providing a harmonizing influence. It is believed to help with balancing of emotional, physical and intellectual endeavors, harmonizing the Ying and Yang forces of the universe. A soothing and calming stone, Agate is thought to bring great strength gradually. This stone is said to aid with the acceptances of oneself, building self confidence. It is also believed that Agate can improve concentration and analytical abilities, resulting in newfound practical solutions.</p>
<h4>About Tsumi</h4>
<p>Tsumi is a brand born from the love of fashion, as well as an inherent need to be original and unique. Each Tsumi accessory is infused by a touch of authentic ethnic flair and is inspired by joyful memories of traveling the world. Tsumi accessories are crafted with an incredible skill, while remaining visionary and creative pieces of contemporary jewelry.</p>
<p>Most of Tsumi accessories are made in either limited quantity or in one unique specimen. Tsumi is also synonymous with an exceptional selection of original and rare materials used to create their stylish accessories. These include semi-precious stones, corals, pearls and crystals, making Tsumi jewelry not only an embodiment of original style, but also an experience.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/tsumi-unique-necklace-lazur-agate-ts181">Tsumi One-Of-A-Kind Azure Agate Necklace TS181</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>WooDoo African Blackwood Earrings W11</title>
		<link>http://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/woodoo-african-blackwood-earrings-pyramid-w11</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2016 14:43:56 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onewithclouds]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/?post_type=product&#038;p=275</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>These wonderful earrings were recreated by WooDoo on our special request in extremely rare and valuable African Blackwood. This request was made specifically to complement WooDoo's magnificent <a href="http://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/woodoo-african-blackwood-ring-w07" target="_blank">African Blackwood W07</a> and <a href="http://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/woodoo-african-blackwood-ring-polyhedral-w08" target="_blank">W08</a> rings. The earrings are complete with delicate and graceful silver pins. Fluent, unique and minimalist, these earrings have a sense of presence and style that is easily recognizable and truly memorable.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/woodoo-african-blackwood-earrings-pyramid-w11">WooDoo African Blackwood Earrings W11</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>These wonderful earrings were recreated by WooDoo on our special request in extremely rare and valuable African Blackwood. This request was made specifically to complement WooDoo&#8217;s magnificent <a href="http://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/woodoo-african-blackwood-ring-w07" target="_blank">African Blackwood W07</a> and <a href="http://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/woodoo-african-blackwood-ring-polyhedral-w08" target="_blank">W08</a> rings. The earrings are complete with delicate and graceful silver pins. Fluent, unique and minimalist, these earrings have a sense of presence and style that is easily recognizable and truly memorable.</p>
<h4>Materials</h4>
<p>African Blackwood is a very rare and expensive wood, exhibiting moisture repellent qualities, as well as incredible dimensional stability. This precious wood is highly valued since the ancient times, when its primary usage purposes included furniture and musical instruments. Considered the original ebony thousand of years ago, this wood was imported to and processed in Ancient Egypt. The name &#8220;ebony&#8217; is actually derived from Egyptian &#8220;hbny&#8221;, while other names for this wood include babanus, grenadilla and mpingo. The African Blackwood tree itself takes about 60 years to mature and originates from seasonally dry regions of Senegal, as well as similar regions east to Eritrea and south to Transvaal.</p>
<p>African Blackwood is a lustrous wood that is one of the hardest and densest in the world.  The color hue of African Blackwood ranges from reddish dark brown and purple to pure black. This timber exhibits little or no straight grain and has an even texture. Extremely durable in terms of resistance to decay, African Blackwood is also moderately resistant to insect attacks. While beautiful and durable, this precious wood is notorious for its blunting effect on wood cutters, making it very difficult to work with either by hand or with machine tools. Although pretty much indiscernible upon completion, African Blackwood has a mild distinctive scent that it emits while being processed. Among many precious woods, African Blackwood is considered one of the very finest timbers to be used in producing turned wood objects.</p>
<h4>About WooDoo</h4>
<p>WooDoo is an incredibly magentic contemporary jewelry brand unlike any other. WooDoo is concerned with creative exploration of space, its geometric properties, as well as the possibilities of their tangible expression. All of this combines into a very original and unique aesthetic. WooDoo&#8217;s works are true artistic explorations of the properties of space. These explorations stem from visions of space that get translated into the physical world by means of minimalist tangible objects. But even after receiving physical form, WooDoo&#8217;s jewelry pieces feel deeply rooted in the realm of creative and visionary.</p>
<p>WooDoo&#8217;s accessories are truly memorable, commanding attention and recognition and are handcrafted from a number of select tactile precious woods, like African Blackwood or Purpleheart Wood. Each of WooDoo&#8217;s jewelry pieces carries an unmistakably modern, contemporary jewelry aesthetic. It is this aesthetic, along with skillful execution that WooDoo&#8217;s accessories owe to the duo of creative designers, standing behind this unique and visionary brand.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/woodoo-african-blackwood-earrings-pyramid-w11">WooDoo African Blackwood Earrings W11</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
