<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>tree crown &#8211; Nuage Showroom</title>
	<atom:link href="http://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product-tag/tree-crown/feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage</link>
	<description>Our Clothing &#38; Accessories</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 01:55:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Moorigin Tree Crown Pendant Silver M11</title>
		<link>http://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/moorigin-tree-crown-pendant-m-silver-m11</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2016 19:13:43 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onewithclouds]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/?post_type=product&#038;p=80</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p><em>The circular arrangement of the crown is reminiscent of the Moon, emanating mysterious elegance...</em></p>
<p>Moorigin accessories, through their minimalist and essential nature, lend themselves well to symbolic interpretation. A tree is one of the most universal symbols of protection and spirituality. Deeply rooted in the ground, but reaching into the skies trees can often be seen as connecting Heaven and Earth. Growing, a tree symbolizes a person's path, as well as continuous cycles of renewal.</p>
<p>Dimensions : 61 x 62 x 0.3 mm<br />
Adjust Chain : 70-76 cm<br />
Material : Stainless Steel<br />
Color : Silver</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/moorigin-tree-crown-pendant-m-silver-m11">Moorigin Tree Crown Pendant Silver M11</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>The circular arrangement of the crown is reminiscent of the Moon, emanating mysterious elegance&#8230;</em></p>
<p>Moorigin accessories, through their minimalist and essential nature, lend themselves well to symbolic interpretation. A tree is one of the most universal symbols of protection and spirituality. Deeply rooted in the ground, but reaching into the skies trees can often be seen as connecting Heaven and Earth. Growing, a tree symbolizes a person&#8217;s path, as well as continuous cycles of renewal.</p>
<h4>Care</h4>
<p>Moorigin accessories are quite comfortable and atmospheric, partly because of their low weight. Although, being lightweight these can bend, despite the fact they&#8217;re made of steel. Please keep this in mind, to prevent bending your lovely Moorigin accessories. Also, make sure to remove them while bathing, taking shower or swimming, as even stainless steel can be prone to some forms of corrosion when exposed to water or humidity. In the event, your accessories do come in contact with water, simply clean them with a soft cloth.</p>
<h4>About Moorigin</h4>
<p>The meaningful design concepts behind the visionary contemporary accessories brand Moorigin can be interpreted as inspired by nature, simple and sensual. Moorigin accessories are developed around bare essentials. These essentials include only the material and the design. Inspired by our planet&#8217;s living environment, the brand embraces some of nature&#8217;s most intricate and enduring forces, such as evolution and structured, orderly chaos. Stemming from a personal vision, unobstructed and uncluttered, Moorigin accessories feel personal, evoking a feeling of atmosphere and sensuality.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage/product/moorigin-tree-crown-pendant-m-silver-m11">Moorigin Tree Crown Pendant Silver M11</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://onewithclouds.github.io/nuage">Nuage Showroom</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
